<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Commissions"
    id="bf2fed0f-d7cd-40b7-b7dd-a6d826bf88db"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A broker completes a product sale to an existing customer and their commission entitlement is captured for subsequent processing&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;The handling of commission payments can be very complex as different commission entitlements and volume thresholds can apply and commission entitlements can occur at different stages in the life-cycle of a product or service (e.g. at initial agreement/sale, on set-up, at some stage during fulfillment). Furthermore commission entitlements can be reversed in some situations and the agreement and payment mechanisms vary for different types of employee/associate. This service domain captures a general commission transaction at the product/service level and assumes that the Commission Agreement service domain provides the appropriate business rules for determining the entitlement, timing, amount and mechanism for payment. The service domain initiates the derived payment typically through Payroll. A more comprehensive design with additional service domains may be required for larger and/or more complex enterprises&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Capture and structure commissionable transactions that are subsequently processed against an existing commission agreement&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Брокер завершает продажу продукта существующему клиенту, и их комиссионные права фиксируются для последующей обработки&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Обработка комиссионных платежей может быть очень сложной, так как могут применяться различные комиссионные права и пороги объема, а комиссионные права могут возникать на разных этапах жизненного цикла продукта или услуги (например, при первоначальном соглашении/продаже, при настройке, на каком-то этапе во время выполнения). Кроме того, в некоторых ситуациях комиссионные могут быть отменены, а механизмы соглашения и оплаты различаются для разных типов сотрудников / ассоциированных сотрудников. Этот домен услуг фиксирует общую транзакцию комиссии на уровне продукта / услуги и предполагает, что домен обслуживания соглашения о комиссии предоставляет соответствующие бизнес-правила для определения права, времени, суммы и механизма оплаты. Домен службы инициирует производный платеж, как правило, через платежную ведомость. Для более крупных и/или сложных предприятий может потребоваться более комплексный проект с дополнительными доменами обслуживания&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Захват и структурирование комиссионных транзакций, которые впоследствии обрабатываются в соответствии с существующим соглашением о комиссии&#xA;&#xA;"/>
