<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Product Combination"
    id="5e207b64-5645-4758-ada3-c8c6f2d45010"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;In external agreements with customers, bundled pricing will often be based on compensation models to simplify operations and fulfill auditing purposes,&#xA;In bank-internal agreements, profit allocation to the respective profit center is based on the result of the combined calculation.&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;Bundle fees can be calculated based on conditions assigned to the bundle only. Combined calculation requires calculation items and results from other SD as input to perform calculations. &#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Product Combination is executing all combined product facilities which cannot be allocated to a single product in the product bundle. The fulfillment will mainly focus on (but is not limited to) the bundled pricing of the Product Combination resulting into fees, charges and equivalents such as bonus points. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Во внешних соглашениях с клиентами пакетное ценообразование часто основывается на моделях компенсации для упрощения операций и выполнения целей аудита,&#xA;Во внутренних договорах банка распределение прибыли в соответствующий центр прибыли основывается на результате комбинированного расчета.&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Сборы за пакет могут быть рассчитаны на основе условий, назначенных только для пакета. Для выполнения комбинированных вычислений требуются элементы вычислений и результаты других SD в качестве входных данных. &#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Комбинация продуктов выполняет все комбинированные средства продукта, которые не могут быть выделены для одного продукта в пакете продукта. Выполнение будет в основном сосредоточено на (но не ограничивается) связанном ценообразовании комбинации продуктов, приводящей к сборам, сборам и эквивалентам, таким как бонусные баллы.&#xA;"/>
