<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Market Analysis"
    id="db1a4702-9569-43c0-8ef0-9555e7510774"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Market analysts, define and develop insights into the market to support different aspects of the banks business &#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain supports the range of market research analysis needed to support business management decisions. It draws on external market research and internally generated business information as necessary. It is used to develop insights into market trends and potential and to evaluate key events that might impact business directly or that of important customers and customer segments&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Analyze internal and external market information sources as necessary to develop specific market insights&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Аналитики рынка, определяют и развивают понимание рынка для поддержки различных аспектов бизнеса банков &#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Эта область услуг поддерживает ряд исследований рынка, необходимых для поддержки решений по управлению бизнесом. Он опирается на исследования внешних рынков и, при необходимости, на внутреннюю деловую информацию. Он используется для анализа рыночных тенденций и потенциала, а также для оценки ключевых событий, которые могут повлиять на бизнес напрямую или важных клиентов и клиентских сегментов&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Анализ внутренних и внешних источников рыночной информации по мере необходимости для разработки конкретных рыночных идей&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Market Analysis&#xA;This service domain supports the broad range of market analysis needed to support business management decisions across the bank. It draws on external market research and internally generated business information as necessary. It is used to develop insights into market trends and potential opportunities/threats. It may also be used to evaluate key events that might impact the bank's business directly or that of important customers and customer segments. A standard set of analytical views can be defined that are maintained. Furthermore the service domain may provide ad-hoc/customized analysis services&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain analyzes internal and external market information sources as necessary to develop specific market insights. It may maintain a collection of predefined market analyses and may also offer specific ad-hoc analysis on request&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain analyzes internal and external market information sources as necessary to develop specific market insights. It may maintain a collection of predefined market analyses and may also offer specific ad-hoc analysis on request&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;External market research is used to develop competitor analysis for bank products as input to a prospect campaign development&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
