<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Contact Routing"
    id="b1f17e26-06c0-45e0-aced-51ce3d0cb8a9"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A customer is self servicing on the E-Branch and uses VoIP to request contact center support. A case is raised against a disputed service change and the customer contact is logged&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;Contact Routing is called from Contact Management to initiate a contact session within an active customer contact. The routing decision can include determining the purpose of the contact, screen pop generation (using CTI) subject ID verification and further determination of contact purpose (than that already determined in the channel or provided by Contact Management). Routing can be optimized for leverage of specialized/qualified servicing resources, have scheduled and load/activity based routing criteria. Contact Routing can collaborate with Contact Manager to support multiple contact sessions in parallel or in series within a single customer contact event as needed.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Contact Routing tracks servicing resource availability, further qualifies and potentially versifies the contact and makes an optimal routing decision. This can include generating a screen pop if CTI is available and support multi channel operations and onward routing of unfinished contacts&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент является самообслуживанием в электронном филиале и использует VoIP для запроса поддержки контакт-центра. Дело возбуждается против спорного изменения службы, и контакт клиента регистрируется&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Маршрутизация контактов вызывается из управления контактами, чтобы инициировать сеанс контактов в активном контакте с клиентом. Решение о маршрутизации может включать определение цели контакта, проверку идентификатора субъекта генерации экранной pop (с помощью CTI) и дальнейшее определение цели контакта (чем это уже определено в канале или предоставлено Управлением контактами). Маршрутизация может быть оптимизирована для использования специализированных / квалифицированных ресурсов обслуживания, иметь запланированные и нагрузки/активности на основе критериев маршрутизации. Маршрутизация контактов может работать совместно с Contact Manager для поддержки нескольких сеансов контактов параллельно или последовательно в рамках одного события контакта с клиентом по мере необходимости.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Следов контакта маршрутизации обслуживания, доступности ресурсов, дальше и потенциально versifies контакт и делает оптимальное решение маршрутизации. Это может включать в себя создание всплывающего экрана, если CTI доступен и поддерживает многоканальные операции и далее маршрутизации незавершенных контактов&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Contact Routing&#xA;Contact Routing is called from Contact Management to identify the next available and most suited servicing resource to handle a servicing session within an active customer contact. Selection is optimized to leverage of specialized/qualified servicing resources based on any known details about the customer and the purpose of their contact with the bank&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;The Contact Routing service domain tracks servicing resource availability and uses any known details about the customer contact (e.g. identity, indicated purpose of call, status of the relationship) to make an optimal routing decision. The routing selection may include matching the required product knowledge/skills to the available servicing resources&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;The Contact Routing service domain tracks servicing resource availability and uses any known details about the customer contact to make an optimal routing decision. The routing selection may include matching the required product knowledge/skills to the available servicing resources&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A high value customer contacts the bank. They have been flagged as a sales prospect and so are routed to the next available rep that is registered as being skilled in the specific product of interest and also experienced in sales&#xA;"/>
