<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Market Research"
    id="aef0506a-a16d-4bd6-a240-f9f9e97d17c6"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A market research department handles the access and consolidation and classification of market research&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain supports general market research for a wide range of uses and sources - including customer and competitor activity and related market assessments. It can combine subscribing to and consolidating market research with supporting on-line/interactive access to market news sources (general not financial market). A more sophisticated implementation will support specific market information requests and the consolidation of gathered intelligence&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Capture market research from multiple sources, classify and store information for retrieval&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Отдел маркетинговых исследований занимается доступом, консолидацией и классификацией маркетинговых исследований&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Эта область услуг поддерживает общие исследования рынка для широкого спектра применений и источников, включая деятельность клиентов и конкурентов и связанные с ними оценки рынка. Он может сочетать подписку и консолидацию маркетинговых исследований с поддержкой онлайн/интерактивного доступа к источникам рыночных новостей (общий, а не финансовый рынок). Более сложная реализация будет поддерживать конкретные запросы рыночной информации и консолидацию собранной информации&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Захватывать маркетинговые исследования из нескольких источников, классифицировать и хранить информацию для поиска&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Market Research&#xA;This service domain supports general market research for a wide range of uses and sources - including customer and competitor activity and related market assessments. It can combine subscribing to and consolidating market research with supporting on-line/interactive access to market news sources (general, not financial market). A more sophisticated implementation will support specific market information requests and the consolidation of gathered intelligence&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain handles the capture of market research from multiple external sources. This can include live feeds, analysis and reports in any form. The information is classified/catalogued and stored for retrieval.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain handles the capture of market research from multiple external sources. This can include live feeds, analysis and reports in any form. The information is classified/catalogued and stored for retrieval.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A market research department handles the access and consolidation and classification of market research&#xA;&#xA;"/>
