<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Card Terminal Operation"
    id="e78a5453-2009-4ca1-931b-be1e5c74cc24"
    documentation="&#xA;&#xA;Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Charge transactions that are submitted by a Merchant through Point of Sale Terminals or Authorization Links are recorded by the Acquiring Bank as they are received and are held until the Merchant reconciles and closes a batch on the Terminal or Cash Register at the end of the day or shift. Transactions contained in batches that are closed by the Merchant are then sent for clearing.&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain maintains a record of the transactions received from each Point of Sale Terminal or Authorization Link used by the Merchants to submit card charges and is used to help the merchant reconcile the transactions at the end of day or shift. The service domain also monitors the operating status of the terminals and handles terminal replacement. Transactions are forwarded to the Card Clearing service domain when the terminal batches are closed by the merchant.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Handle POS operations including processing, capture and tracking of the transactions originating at the Point of Sale devices.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Проводки по расходам, отправляемые продавцом через терминалы торговых точек или авторизационные ссылки, регистрируются банком-эквайером по мере их получения и удерживаются до тех пор, пока продавец не сверит и не закроет пакет на терминале или кассовом аппарате в конце дня или смены. Транзакции, содержащиеся в пакетах, которые закрываются продавцом, затем отправляются для очистки.&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен услуг ведет учет транзакций, полученных из каждой точки терминала продажи или ссылки авторизации, используемой продавцами для отправки платежей по карте, и используется, чтобы помочь продавцу согласовать транзакции в конце дня или смены. Сервисный домен также контролирует рабочее состояние терминалов и осуществляет замену терминалов. Транзакции пересылаются в домен сервиса клиринга карт, когда пакеты терминала закрываются продавцом.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Обработка операций POS, включая обработку, захват и отслеживание транзакций, порождаются в POS устройствах&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Card Terminal Operation&#xA;This service domain maintains a record of the transactions received from each Point of Sale Terminal or Authorization Link used by the Merchants to submit card charges and is used to help the merchant reconcile the transactions at the end of day or shift. Transactions are forwarded to the Card Clearing service domain when the terminal batches are closed by the merchant. The service domain also monitors the operating status of the terminals and handles terminal replacement&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain handle POS operations including processing, capture and tracking of the transactions originating at the Point of Sale devices&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;Charge transactions that are submitted by a Merchant through Point of Sale Terminals or Authorization Links are recorded by the Acquiring Bank as they are received and are held until the Merchant reconciles and closes a batch on the Terminal or Cash Register at the end of the day or shift&#xA;"/>
