<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Case"
    id="bdba5d90-4777-4c6e-a8a1-f29d5c8f280b"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A case resolution operator works through the resolution of a case, following the established process for the specific case - in this case a disputed charge that is below a threshold allowing the credit to be charged to the merchant&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;Case resolution tasks follow specific procedures for the type of case involved. Case resolution can be quick by applying resolution rules and obtaining additional authorization as necessary, or they can be long living activities, for example where documentation is requested and has to be retrieved from merchants before the disputed issue can finally be ruled upon. A wide range of case types can be expected&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Initiate, track, resolve and report on customer cases (issues that typically require corrective response to some financial transaction)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Оператор разрешения дела работает через разрешение дела, следуя установленному процессу для конкретного случая - в этом случае оспариваемая плата, которая ниже порога, позволяющего кредит взиматься с торговца&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Решение задач случае следовать конкретные процедуры для типа делом занимаются. Разрешение дел может быть быстрым путем применения правил разрешения и получения дополнительного разрешения по мере необходимости, или они могут быть долгоживущей деятельностью, например, когда документация запрашивается и должна быть получена от торговцев, прежде чем спорный вопрос может быть окончательно решен. Можно ожидать широкий спектр типов случаев&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Инициирование, отслеживание, разрешение и отчет по обращениям клиентов (проблемы, которые обычно требуют корректирующего ответа на некоторые финансовые транзакции)&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Customer Case&#xA;Case resolution tasks follow specific procedures for the type of case involved. Case resolution can be quick by applying resolution rules and obtaining additional authorization as necessary, or they can be long living activities, for example where documentation is requested and has to be retrieved from merchants or other interested parties before the disputed issue can finally be ruled upon. A wide range of case types can be expected&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain handles the initiation, tracking, resolution and reporting on customer cases (issues that typically require corrective response to some financial transaction)&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A case resolution operator works through the resolution of a case, following the established process for the specific case - in this case a disputed charge that is below a threshold allowing the credit to be charged to the merchant&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
