<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="eTrading Workbench"
    id="78a44743-68fb-43d0-b0e8-c5c8e8097ccc"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A consumer customer logs on to the E-branch web portal to access their e-trading account, tracks prices and research relating to his portfolio and executes and sale/purchase pair of transactions.&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This capability administers the fulfillment of an E-trading financial facility for consumer customers. Trades can be routed and executed in the appropriate exchange individually or it is possible for some situations that a more sophisticated batching &amp; netting approach can be considered as appropriate. The facility can embed structured access to Market Data Dissemination Administration and Market Data Dissemination Operation service domains for subscription market data feeds as necessary. The customer agreement and service access mechanisms use the standard Customer Agreement, Party Profile &amp; E-Branch service domains for access and execution.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Operate the distributed consumer e-trading facility (local application and network connectivity to the bank). This environment hosts/supports a financial facility type product (service domain Consumer Investments) that customer use to trade securities on their own account through the bank. From the workbench environment using consumer investments a customer can initiate the execution of securities trades against their facility as well as applying service/facility fees and charges. The consumer investments capability accessed through the workbench integrates with the supporting customer accounting facilities which can include more complex margin accounts (and margin call initiation) as necessary&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Потребительский клиент входит на веб-портал электронного филиала для доступа к своему электронному торговому счету, отслеживает цены и исследования, связанные с его портфелем, а также выполняет сделки купли-продажи.&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Эта возможность управляет выполнением финансового механизма электронной торговли для клиентов-потребителей. Сделки могут быть направлены и выполнены в соответствующей бирже индивидуально или это возможно в некоторых ситуациях, что более сложный подход дозирования и взаимозачета можно считать целесообразным. Этот механизм может обеспечивать структурированный доступ к управлению распространением рыночных данных и доменам обслуживания операций по распространению рыночных данных для подпискных каналов рыночных данных по мере необходимости. Клиентское соглашение и механизмы доступа к услугам используют стандартное клиентское соглашение, профиль участника и Домены обслуживания E-филиала для доступа и выполнения.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Управление распределенной электронной торговой системой (локальное приложение и сетевое подключение к банку). В этой среде размещается / поддерживается продукт типа финансового средства (service domain Consumer Investments), который клиент использует для торговли ценными бумагами за свой счет через банк. Из среды workbench, используя потребительские инвестиции, клиент может инициировать совершение сделок с ценными бумагами против своего объекта, а также применять плату за услуги/Услуги и сборы. Возможность потребительских инвестиций, доступная через workbench, интегрируется с поддерживающими средствами учета клиентов, которые могут включать более сложные маржинальные счета (и инициирование маржинального вызова) по мере необходимости&#xA;&#xA;"/>
