<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Remittances"
    id="4f7d4caf-013c-4241-9278-10bcc54798bf"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;An established customer transfers an amount to an overseas account. As this is a recurring transaction, the details are maintained and updated as needed each time&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain supports cash remittance services for consumer and business customers. Payments are made to other accounts within the bank, other banks and possibly internationally using whatever payments mechanism is suited to the transaction (See Payments Execution). The service domain is modeled as a transaction, though it may reference prior remittance activity for repeated transactions.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Orchestrate national and international payment and remittance services. (Retain repeat transaction details where appropriate)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Установленный клиент переводит сумму на зарубежный счет. Поскольку это повторяющаяся транзакция, подробные данные сохраняются и обновляются по мере необходимости каждый раз&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен услуг поддерживает услуги денежных переводов для потребителей и бизнес-клиентов. Платежи осуществляются на другие счета в банке, других банках и, возможно, на международном уровне с использованием любого механизма платежей, подходящего для транзакции (см. Выполнение платежей). Домен службы моделируется как транзакция, хотя он может ссылаться на предыдущие операции перевода для повторяющихся транзакций.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Организация национальных и международных платежей и денежных переводов. (При необходимости сохраните сведения о повторной транзакции)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Remittance&#xA;This service domain supports payment services for consumer and business customers. Payments are made to other accounts within the bank, other banks and possibly internationally using whatever payments mechanism is suited to the transaction (See Payments Order/Execution). The service domain can support single transactions, or manage repeating/scheduled payments if requested&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain provides a customer payment service. It captures the payer and payee details and other key properties of the payment and orchestrates the transaction. It provides support for repeating/scheduled payments&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;An established customer transfers an amount from their current account to an overseas account for a family member. As this is a recurring transaction, the details are maintained and updated as necessary"/>
