<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Card Network Participant Facility"
    id="8ad63139-fe3b-4a2f-aea2-7eee0d3104f0"
    documentation="&#xA;&#xA;Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Cards issued by banks are affiliated with one of many international Card Networks, such as Visa, Master Card, Diners, American Express, etc. The Card Network signs up Acquiring Banks for recruiting and setting up accounts for merchants and Issuing Banks for issuing cards to its customers.&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain is used by the Card Network for setting up Acquiring and Issuing Bank accounts and their terms and conditions.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Orchestrate the activities related to the inclusion of new Acquirers and Issuers in the Card Network, their terms and conditions and their status.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Карты, выпущенные банками, связаны с одной из многих международных карточных сетей, таких как Visa, MasterCard, Diners, American Express и др. Сеть карт регистрирует банки-эквайеры для пополнения и открытия счетов торговцам и банкам-эмитентам для выпуска карт своим клиентам.&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот сервисный домен используется карточной сетью для настройки банковских счетов эквайринга и выдачи, а также их условий.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Организовывать деятельность, связанную с включением новых эквайеров и эмитентов в карточную сеть, их условиями и статусом.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Card Network Participant Facility&#xA;Cards issued by banks are affiliated with one of many international Card Networks, such as Visa, Master Card, Diners, American Express. This service domain is used by the Card Network for setting up Acquiring and Issuing Bank accounts and their terms and conditions.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain orchestrates the activities related to the inclusion of new Acquirers and Issuers in the Card Network, their terms and conditions and their status&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;The Card Network signs up Acquiring Banks for recruiting and setting up accounts for merchants and Issuing Banks for issuing cards to its customers&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
