<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Delinquent Account Handling (card)"
    id="2ffbbf85-0575-4501-bf56-0fd0665adfbc"
    documentation="&#xA;&#xA;Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;When a Card Account is assessed to be at a high risk of default, such as a Charge Card Account with high out of pattern outstandings or a Credit Card Account with significant aged balances, attempts are made to elicit the payment of the outstanding amounts or to limit further increase in risk through optimal strategies for contacting the customer and inducing payment of the outstanding amount. The Card may continue to maintain charging privileges at this stage.&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain determines and executes strategies for eliciting payment from high risk Card Accounts. These strategies may include communicating with the customer through text messages, emails or phone calls, reducing the credit line or blocking the card to prevent further increase in risk, or to cancel the card and transfer it to Card Collections.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Handle delinquent accounts (for active cards) for follow-up of payments due through periodic review and contacts. This process ends when the card account is cancelled and is transferred to Card Collections.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Когда карточный счет оценивается как подверженный высокому риску дефолта, например, счет платежной карты с высокими нестандартными показателями или счет кредитной карты со значительными устаревшими балансами, предпринимаются попытки получить оплату непогашенных сумм или ограничить дальнейшее увеличение риска с помощью оптимальных стратегий для связи с клиентом и побуждения оплаты непогашенной суммы. На этом этапе карта может продолжать поддерживать привилегии зарядки.&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен услуг определяет и выполняет стратегии получения платежей с карточных счетов высокого риска. Эти стратегии могут включать в себя общение с клиентом посредством текстовых сообщений, электронных писем или телефонных звонков, уменьшение кредитной линии или блокирование карты для предотвращения дальнейшего увеличения риска или для отмены карты и передачи ее в коллекции карт.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Обработка просроченных счетов (для активных карт) для отслеживания платежей, подлежащих периодическому обзору и контактам. Этот процесс заканчивается, когда карточный счет отменяется и переносится в карточные коллекции.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Card Delinquent Account Handling&#xA;This service domain determines and executes strategies for eliciting payment from high risk Card Accounts. These strategies may include communicating with the customer through text messages, emails or phone calls. The Card may continue to maintain charging privileges at this stage. Eventually it can be necessary to reduce the credit line or block the card to prevent further increase in risk, or to cancel the card and transfer it to Card Collections. &#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain handles delinquent accounts (for active cards) for follow-up of payments due through periodic review and contacts. This process ends when the card account is cancelled and is transferred to Card Collections&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;When a Card Account is assessed to be at a high risk of default, such as a Charge Card Account with high out of pattern outstandings or a Credit Card Account with significant aged balances, attempts are made to elicit the payment of the outstanding amounts or to limit further increase in risk&#xA;"/>
