<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Party Data Management"
    id="ac8f72fb-4cb1-415d-afa7-631b6f77bed4"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Party legal entity details are obtained for selection in an internal sales campaign&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain maintains a comprehensive set of party reference information. This has significantly different content and functionality depending on party/customer type. The main reference information is legal entity structure. It is possible that additional party type specific reference service domains will be added in later versions of the model (for example reference details specific to customer types, brokers, agents, counterparties, sub-custodians etc.)&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Maintain a comprehensive set of party reference details, including legal entity structure, demographics, administrative, KYC related properties, status and activity summaries&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Сведения о юридическом лице стороны получены для выбора во внутренней кампании продаж&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен сохраняет полный набор справочной информации. Это имеет значительно различное содержание и функциональность в зависимости от типа партии/клиента. Основная справочная информация-структура юридического лица. Возможно, что в более поздних версиях модели будут добавлены дополнительные Домены справочной службы для конкретных типов сторон (например, справочные сведения, относящиеся к типам клиентов, брокерам, агентам, контрагентам, суб-кастодианам и т. д.).)&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Поддерживать полный набор группа реквизитов, в том числе юридическое лицо структуры, демографии, административного, ЗСК свойства, состояния и активности резюме&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Party Data Management&#xA;This service domain maintains a view of the legal entity structure of a party with which the bank does business. It records different reference information detail depending on the type of entity - e.g. an individual/household, company or business partner. Where appropriate the service domain can maintain ratings and key financial properties of the entity where this has a bearing on the bank relationship.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains details of the legal entity structure of the party including dependents and associations for individuals and ownership/subsidiary structures for corporations. Some financial indicators and product coverage/activity details can be included where this defines the nature of the legal entity relationship in particular for corporate entities.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains details of the legal entity structure of the party including dependents and associations for individuals and ownership/subsidiary structures for corporations.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;Party legal entity details are checked for the financial booking of a major loan.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
