<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Market Data Switch Operation"
    id="fe6bb596-b2a7-458b-8cb2-5bbf32c455a6"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A trader request access to a market data feed during a trading session&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This facility handles the day to day operation of the information dissemination capability (a high performance/availability requirement) typically addressing trading requirements. It references the Market Data Feed Entitlement and Associated Market Feed Agreements to confirm eligibility for requested services. The dissemination mechanism/switch will support composite pages of data for certain users and can combine internally published information with external feeds where appropriate&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Operate the day to day information distribution facility in compliance with administered access rights and the demand and availability of subscribed information feed services. Note content is provided by the Market Feed Operation service domain for external feeds. Internal information can also be published over the channel from various content sources.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Трейдер запрашивает доступ к ленте рыночных данных во время торговой сессии&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот механизм обеспечивает повседневное функционирование механизма распространения информации (требование высокой производительности/доступности), который, как правило, отвечает торговым требованиям. Он ссылается на право на получение рыночных данных и соответствующие соглашения о предоставлении рыночных данных для подтверждения права на запрашиваемые услуги. Механизм распространения / переключатель будет поддерживать составные страницы данных для определенных пользователей и может объединять опубликованную внутри страны информацию с внешними каналами, где это необходимо&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Осуществлять повседневную деятельность по распространению информации в соответствии с правами доступа, а также с требованиями и доступностью подписанных на рассылку информационных услуг. Содержание записки, представленной на рынке корма для домена на обслуживание внешних каналов. Внутренняя информация также может быть опубликована по каналу из различных источников контента.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Market Data Switch Operation&#xA;This facility handles the real-time operation of the market information dissemination switch that is typically used to support trading and investment functions. It references the access entitlement to services for users maintained by the Market Data Switch Administration service domain (there can be complex rules governing access to various feeds). The dissemination mechanism/switch may support composite pages of data and interactive service requests. It may also support internally published information such as bank rates defined by the bank's treasury unit&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain operates the internal information distribution facility/switch in compliance with administered external subscription information feed service access rights. Note the content is retrieved by the Market Feed Operation service domain from the various external feed services. Internal information can also be published over the switch from various bank sources (such as bank rates provided by treasury).&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain operates the internal information distribution facility/switch in compliance with administered external subscription information feed service access rights. Note the content is retrieved by the Market Feed Operation service domain from the various external feed services. Internal&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A bank trader request access to a market data feed at their dealing position during a trading session&#xA;"/>
