<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Event History"
    id="156bf99a-36a3-442b-a256-b392d56c7128"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A customer contacts the call center to enquire about account transactions and during the dialogue the CSR captures a life event (e.g. the customer is moving house). The contact details and life event are captured in the customer history&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;The service domain captures a wide range of customer events to build a comprehensive history of customer activity that can support subsequent behavioral analysis. This includes key sales/proposal events, relationship management events, product delivery events, detected customer triggers (typically gleaned during servicing dialogues) and possibly externally sourced customer activity. The assembled data is made available for behavioral analysis and for more general reference (as might be used for relationship management for example). Note servicing activity for root cause analysis is captured elsewhere&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Capture, classify and store relationship, servicing and product related customer events. In addition to transactional details, the log can capture life/relationship events&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент связывается с колл-центром, чтобы узнать о транзакциях по счету, и во время диалога CSR фиксирует событие жизни (например, клиент перемещает дом). Контактные данные и события фиксируются в истории клиента &#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Домен обслуживания фиксирует широкий спектр событий клиента для построения полной истории активности клиента, которая может поддерживать последующий анализ поведения. Это включает в себя ключевые события продаж / предложения, события управления отношениями, события доставки продукта, обнаруженные триггеры клиентов (обычно получаемые во время диалогов обслуживания) и, возможно, внешнюю активность клиентов. Собранные данные доступны для поведенческого анализа и для более общего использования (например, для управления отношениями). Примечание действия по обслуживанию для анализа причин фиксируется в другом месте&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Захват, классифицировать и хранить отношения, обслуживание и связанные с продуктом события клиентов. В дополнение к транзакционным деталям, журнал может фиксировать события жизни / отношений&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Customer Event History&#xA;The service domain captures a wide range of customer events to build a comprehensive history of customer activity that can support subsequent behavioral analysis. This includes key sales/proposal events, relationship management events, product delivery events, detected customer triggers (typically gleaned during servicing dialogues) and possibly externally sourced customer activity. The assembled data is made available for behavioral analysis and for more general reference (as might be used for relationship management for example).&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain captures, classifies and stores relationship, servicing and product fulfillment related customer events. In addition to servicing and product transaction details, the log can capture life/relationship events that are revealed during customer exchanges.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain captures, classifies and stores relationship, servicing and product fulfillment related customer events. In addition to servicing and product transaction details, the log can capture life/relationship events that are revealed during customer exchanges.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A customer contacts the call center to enquire about account transactions and during the dialogue the servicing representative detects a life event (e.g. the customer is moving house). The contact details and life event are captured in the customer history.&#xA;&#xA;"/>
