<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Access Entitlement"
    id="477bc971-f598-4c58-8297-00a15768be5c"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A consumer customer contacts the call center and her access profile is used to determine what products and services can be accessed through this channel&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This profile is used for servicing and fulfillment controls covering products, services and channel/device usage entitlements. It is referenced for channel access controls and utilization limits&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Maintains the details of the products services and channel access that the customer has in place. This profile is referenced in servicing and fulfillment activity. The view may also be compared to the full range of eligible products and services to identify business development opportunities.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент-потребитель обращается в центр обработки вызовов, и его профиль доступа используется для определения того, к каким продуктам и услугам можно получить доступ через этот канал&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот профиль используется для обслуживания и контроля выполнения, охватывающих продукты, услуги и права использования канала/устройства. Оно снабжен ссылками для управлений доступом канала и пределов использования&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Поддерживает детали обслуживаний продуктов и доступа канала который клиент имеет на месте. На этот профиль ссылаются в действии обслуживания и выполнения. Это мнение можно также сравнить с полным спектром приемлемых продуктов и услуг для определения возможностей развития бизнеса.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Customer Access Entitlement&#xA;This profile is used for servicing and fulfillment controls covering products, services and channel/device usage entitlements. It is referenced for channel access control and utilization limits that may span multiple products. For example there can be a limit on total ATM withdrawals for a customer for all active products over a 24 hour period&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains the details of the allowed channel/device based access to products and services that the customer has in place.  This profile is referenced in servicing and fulfillment activity and may include customer preferences and access limits/constraints that span multiple products&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;Maintains the details of the allowed channel/device based access to products and services that the customer has in place. This profile is referenced in servicing and fulfillment activity and may include customer preferences and access limits/constraints that span multiple products&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A consumer customer contacts the call center and her access profile is used to determine what products and services can be accessed through this channel"/>
