<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Product Directory"
    id="f8ce5fda-b000-4044-a91d-c901612b8b2f"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;Available product components, functions and features are registered and stored in SD Product Directory, ready to be used by SD Product Design.&#xA;New product specifications from Q&amp;E SDs will be registered in SD Product Directory, with all its functions, features, price models etc. available in the O&amp;E SDs as operational products, and with the sales product, which includes terms and conditions, in SD Sales Product.&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Keep information about the basic product building blocks, represented as Product Components with Functions and Features, as well as the completed product specification from SD Product Design.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Имеющиеся компоненты, функции и характеристики продукта зарегистрированы и сохранены в директории продукта SD, готовой быть использованным оформлением изделия SD.&#xA;Новые технические характеристики изделия от Q&amp;E SDs будут зарегистрированы в директории продукта SD, с всеми своими функциями, характеристиками, моделями цены etc. доступный в O&amp;E SDs как рабочие продукты, и с продуктом сбываний, который включает термины и условия, в продукте Сбываний SD.&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Хранить информацию об основных строительных блоках продукта, представленных в виде компонентов продукта с функциями и возможностями, а также полную спецификацию продукта из SD Product Design.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Product Directory&#xA;The product directory service domain provides a central service to reference product specifications and related details. The broad range of specification information available includes: product feature descriptions; pricing and eligibility requirements used in sales and on-boarding; servicing support and guidelines; and operational and production requirements&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains a comprehensive directory of the bank's products and services. It can be referenced to obtain product details used to support activities including product selection, sales and marketing, on-boarding, servicing and product fulfillment.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains a comprehensive directory of the bank's products and services. It can be referenced to obtain product details used to support activities including product selection, sales and marketing, on-boarding, servicing and product fulfillment.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A customer accesses the product directory to obtain product feature descriptions, eligibility and pricing guidelines&#xA;&#xA;"/>
