<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Account Recovery"
    id="1ed107eb-1b9e-4c10-b72c-6cde7579c648"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A non-performing customer account is handed over for recovery after the normal relationship management efforts have failed. Additional authority is provided to renegotiate/structure the account to enable the customer to attempt recovery. This restructuring can result in write downs that need to be booked appropriately&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;Handles the recovery of distressed accounts that have exceeded standard late/payment handling but have not yet been fully written off and passed to collections. The restructuring can involve partial write downs and leveraging any tax or other program of assistance that can be applied. The situation is managed until the account is recovered or a decision made to pass the account over to collections&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Handle recovery for a customer account where the standard recovery arrangements have been exhausted and a recovery plan is needed, which can include some degree of principal right-down and repayment restructuring&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Неработающая учетная запись клиента передается для восстановления после того, как обычные усилия по управлению отношениями потерпели неудачу. Дополнительные полномочия предоставляются пересмотреть / структурировать учетную запись, чтобы позволить клиенту попытаться восстановления. Такая реструктуризация может привести к списанию, которое необходимо забронировать надлежащим образом&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Обрабатывает восстановление проблемных счетов, которые превысили стандартную обработку просроченных платежей, но еще не были полностью списаны и переданы в _коллекшен_. Реструктуризация может включать частичное списание и использование любых налогов или других программ помощи, которые могут быть применены. Ситуация управляется до восстановления учетной записи или принятия решения о передаче учетной записи в _коллекшен_&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Обработка восстановления для клиентского счета, где стандартные механизмы восстановления были исчерпаны и необходим план восстановления, который может включать некоторую степень основного права вниз и реструктуризации погашения&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Account Recovery&#xA;Handles the recovery of distressed accounts that have exceeded standard late/payment handling but have not yet been fully written off and passed to collections. The restructuring can involve partial write downs and leveraging any tax or other program of assistance that can be applied. The situation is managed until the account is recovered or a decision made to pass the account over to collections&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain handles the restructuring of a distressed account (loan) after standard recovery procedures have been exhausted&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;Non-performing customer account is handed over for recovery after the normal relationship management efforts have failed. Additional authority is provided to renegotiate/structure the account to enable the customer to attempt recovery. It can result in write downs that need to be booked appropriatly&#xA;&#xA;"/>
