<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Position Management"
    id="5cd7bb82-379f-49f6-8818-5a691b98b5d8"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;A trading department maintains cross currency positions across its overall dealing activity, limiting activity as limits are approached&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;This service domain is intended to address complex composite positions that are built from multiple product transactions and financial balances. The position analysis can include current account balances as well as factoring in more complex known and projected cash flows that can arise from longer life instruments. It can include sensitivity weightings for different contributing factors. Other composite positions may relate to a large corporation's consolidated credit position. Most positions will build from account booked data, though there can be positions that will use more volatile data sources such as deal capture data.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Maintain on-line and near-time cross account complex positions. Includes consolidated currency, instrument, sector and counterparty views as appropriate&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Торговый отдел поддерживает кросс-валютные _статусы_ по всей своей общей дилинговой деятельности, ограничивая активность по мере приближения лимитов&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Эта область обслуживания предназначена для решения сложных составных _статусов_, которые строятся из нескольких проводок по продуктам и финансовых балансов. Анализ положения может включать сальдо текущего счета, а также Факторинг в более сложных известных и прогнозируемых денежных потоках, которые могут возникнуть из более долгосрочных инструментов. Он может включать веса чувствительности для различных способствующих факторов. Другие составные _статусы_ могут относиться к консолидированной кредитному статусу_ крупной корпорации. Большинство _статусов_ будет строиться из данных по счету, хотя могут быть _статусы_, которые будут использовать более изменчивые источники данных, такие как данные захвата сделок.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Ведение сложных _статусов_ в режиме онлайн и в ближайшее время. Включает консолидированную валюту, инструмент, сектор и мнения контрагентов по мере необходимости&#xA;"/>
