<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Savings Account"
    id="1f09835e-cb20-4ed2-832b-22122d354b56"
    documentation="Разница между Сберегательным счетом и Депозитным счетом: при оформлении сберегательного счета необходимо поместить на него определенную сумму, значительно меньшую, как правило, чем при депозите. Ее можно пополнять любыми суммами и нерегулярно. У такого вклада не оговаривается срок вклада. При этом ставка является плавающей и пересматривается в зависимости от рыночной ситуации. В свою очередь все накопленные деньги или их часть можно снять в любой момент. Снимая деньги со сберегательного счета, пеню платить не надо, не теряются при этом и накопленные проценты.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; Example of use:&#xA;A customer transfers money from a current account to savings account in order to obtain a better rate of interest.&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;A savings account does not have the full facilities of a current account e.g. checking. &#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Fulfill a savings account&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Клиент переводит деньги с текущего счета на сберегательный, чтобы получить более высокую процентную ставку.&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Сберегательный счет не имеет всех возможностей текущего счета, например, чекового. &#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Выполнить сберегательный счет&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Savings Account&#xA;The savings account product may share many features with a standard bank current account (e.g. standing orders, direct debits, payments and deposit services) with some constraints/limitations. There can be restrictions on the amount and frequency of withdrawals with an associated fee/penalty structure to offset higher interest benefits. Sweep mechanisms linked to other products (current account) can also be supported.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain orchestrates a consumer savings account. The typical range of services and fees covers payments from and scheduled and ad-hoc deposits to the account, standing orders, sweeps, and liens.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain orchestrates a consumer savings account. The typical range of services and fees covers payments from and scheduled and ad-hoc deposits to the account, standing orders, sweeps, and liens.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A customer transfers money from a current account to savings account in order to obtain a better rate of interest.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
