<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="E-Branch Operations"
    id="3049efbc-a429-4d99-8a1d-a5c9ca2237b4"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A day in the life of a web based banking service, dynamically assigns traffic across processing capabilities to minimize response delays&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This is the operating schedule for the E-branch production systems, including access checks, load balancing and device failure and recovery handling - typically a complex 24/7 operation. It can include computer telephony integration (CTI) with branch and call center channels. Note the on-line facilities should match teller and ATM customer viewpoints making allowances for the self serve nature of the dialogue and channel limitations as necessary&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Operate the on-line electronic/web branch capabilities - control access and load balance across available communications and processing resources to optimize performance/availability&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;День в жизни веб-банкинга, динамически распределяет трафик между возможностями обработки, чтобы минимизировать задержки ответа&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Это график работы производственных систем E-branch, включающий проверку доступа, балансировку нагрузки, отказы устройств и обработку восстановления - как правило, сложная операция 24/7. Это может включать интеграцию компьютерной телефонии (CTI) с каналами филиала и центра обработки вызовов. Обратите внимание, онлайн-услуги должны соответствовать рассказчика и точки зрения клиента банкомат делает пособия для самостоятельной служить характер диалога и ограничения канала по мере необходимости&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;:: Управление возможностями электронного / веб-филиала в режиме онлайн-управление доступом и распределением нагрузки между доступными коммуникационными и процессинговыми ресурсами для оптимизации производительности / доступности&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Бизнес-домен: &#xD;&#xA;Операции по продуктам и услугам, предоставляемым через интернет-канал&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - E-Branch Operations&#xA;This service domain operates the E-branch production systems conforming to planned service schedules. It handles customer and non-customer access checks, performs device load balancing and device failure and recovery handling - typically supporting a high performance 24/7 operation. It can include the integration of computer telephony integration (CTI) with branch and call center channels&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain operates the bank's on-line web based electronic branch capabilities - controlling access and load balancing across available communications and processing resources to optimize performance/availability&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain operates the bank's on-line web based electronic branch capabilities - controlling access and load balancing across available communications and processing resources to optimize performance/availability&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;Customers and non-bank customers browse the products and services available at the bank&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
