<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Billing"
    id="67ebbc06-ca98-4561-86e2-d9cb97f6abc1"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;An invoice is raised for the fees and commissions applicable to a managed investment portfolio&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;This service domain provides a general customer billing capability. The service domain is provided with the applicable fees and charges that are authorized for invoicing typically by the product or service fulfillment service domain. Processing can include verification and authorizations steps and the invoice could be issued as a single transaction or a schedule of transactions. Subsequent payment is tracked by Accounts Receivable&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Provide (central) services to compose, issue and track customer billing and invoices (see also accounts receivable)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Выставляется счет на оплату комиссий, применимых к управляемому инвестиционному портфелю&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Этот домен службы предоставляет общие возможности выставления счетов клиентам. Домен услуг предоставляется с применимыми сборами и сборами, которые разрешены для выставления счетов, как правило, доменом обслуживания продуктов или услуг. Обработка может включать этапы проверки и авторизации, а счет-фактура может быть выдан в виде одной транзакции или графика транзакций. Последующий платеж отслеживается по дебиторской задолженности&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Предоставление (централизованных) услуг по составлению, выдаче и отслеживанию счетов и счетов клиентов (см. также расчеты с клиентами)&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Customer Billing&#xA;This service domain provides a general customer billing service. The service domain is provided with the applicable fees and charges that are authorized for invoicing typically by a product or service fulfillment service domain. Processing can include verification and authorizations steps and the invoice could be issued as a single transaction or a schedule of transactions.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domains provides a central service to compose, issue and track customer billing and invoices&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;Provides a central service to compose, issue and track customer billing and invoices&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;An invoice is raised for the fees and commissions applicable to a managed investment portfolio"/>
