<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Behavioral Insights"
    id="8dbb2b17-0c07-42ac-b18f-82bb8eb15ef4"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A regular analysis of customer event histories is used to update the maintained range of customer behavioral insights. The update results are notified to the Party Data Management and Party Profile Service Domains as appropriate&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain references the data assembled by service domain Customer Event History to develop behavioral insights into customers. This analysis can support sales and marketing activity (e.g. by determining the likely response to sales efforts based on passed performance) as well as identifying changes in status and behavior that might influence the desired product mix for a customer. The actual analysis routines are developed in the Analytics area&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Apply behavioral analysis to customer event history to maintain ratings/scores (such as propensity to buy) and detect life events or trends&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Регулярный анализ истории событий клиентов используется для обновления поддерживаемого диапазона анализа поведения клиентов. Результаты обновления будет сообщено руководству партии данных и профиля участника доменов сервиса&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен службы ссылается на данные, собранные с помощью журнала событий клиентов домена службы, для разработки поведенческих представлений о клиентах. Этот анализ может поддерживать продажи и маркетинговую деятельность (например, путем определения вероятной реакции на усилия по продажам на основе пройденной производительности), а также выявления изменений в статусе и поведении, которые могут повлиять на желаемый ассортимент продукции для клиента. Фактические процедуры анализа разрабатываются в области аналитики&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Применение поведенческого анализа к истории событий клиентов для поддержания рейтингов/оценок (например, склонности к покупке) и выявления событий или тенденций в жизни.&#xA;&#xA;Customer Behavioral Insights&#xA;This service domain handles the development, maintenance and continual assessment and refinement of the collection of customer behavior models that are deployed across the bank. This includes more general analyses for sales, operational behavior, relationship development and specific behaviors such as credit and fraud detection. Customer can cover consumer, corporate and merchant behavior for some behavioral models/scanners&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain handles the design and maintenance of a portfolio of customer behavior models that might be used in all aspects of customer relationship development, sales, servicing and product fulfillment&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain handles the design and maintenance of a portfolio of customer behavior models that might be used in all aspects of customer relationship development, sales, servicing and product fulfillment&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A customer 'propensity to buy model' algorithm is updated to take account of additional transaction utilization data that is available&#xA;"/>
