<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Trading Book Oversight"
    id="821e367c-b8ca-455b-a378-76a90a680479"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;End of day trade analysis consolidates and activity report that highlights trading activity that approaches or breaches position limits. The trades behind the exceptions are included as a basis for assessing the causes for unwanted activity&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This is a front/middle office oversight function for trading books, typically managing specific books/positions (such as a currency book) with the intention of partitioning trading activity across the trading team, setting skill appropriate activity boundaries and trading position limits and managing trader related market risks. Trading positions can be maintained in real-time to prevent breaches, and activity can be analyzed after the event to detect and respond/mitigate breaches&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Define and track trading book activity against the established trading rules/entitlements and limits&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Анализ сделок на конец дня консолидирует и отчет о деятельности, в котором освещается торговая деятельность, которая приближается или нарушает лимиты позиций. Сделки, стоящие за исключениями, включены в качестве основы для оценки причин нежелательной активности&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Это функция надзора переднего / среднего офиса за торговыми книгами, обычно управляющая конкретными книгами/позициями (например, валютной книгой) с целью разделения торговой деятельности по всей торговой команде, установления границ соответствующей деятельности и ограничений торговой позиции и управления связанными с трейдером рыночными рисками. Торговые позиции могут поддерживаться в режиме реального времени для предотвращения нарушений, а активность может быть проанализирована после события для обнаружения и реагирования/смягчения нарушений&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Определение и отслеживание активности торгового портфеля в соответствии с установленными торговыми правилами/правами и лимитами&#xA;&#xA;"/>
