<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Asset &amp; Liability Management"
    id="0ce9e132-52ce-4877-a9f8-6d1aad05ca82"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;The bank's Asset &amp; Liability committee meets regularly to refine the financial policies governing the asset and liability position of the bank and to review major pending deals&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain recognizes that most banks will operate a senior policy and governance function to oversee the bank's overall asset and liability make-up and direct activity, allocate capital and define polices to ensure the bank remains within its desired profile. As a senior management team it will rely on analysis and reports&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  A central policy and direction capability that reviews consolidated bank P&amp;L profile and performance and defines and directs asset and liability policies. Also sanctions and/or influences large transactions&#xA;&#xA;Documentation&#xA; A central policy and direction capability that reviews consolidated bank P&amp;L profile and performance and defines and directs asset and liability policies. Also sanctions and/or influences large transactions&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Комитет банка по активам и пассивам регулярно проводит заседания для уточнения финансовой политики, регулирующей положение банка по активам и пассивам, а также для рассмотрения крупных незавершенных сделок&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен служба признает, что большинство банков будет работать старшим политики и функции управления надзора за общей активами и пассивами банка и прямого действия, распределения капитала и определение политики обеспечения банка остается в пределах нужного профиля. Как команда высшего руководства она будет полагаться на анализ и отчеты&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Централизованная политика и возможности управления, которая рассматривает консолидированный профиль P &amp; L банка и производительность и определяет и направляет политику активов и обязательств. Также санкции и / или влияние на крупные сделки&#xA;&#xA;Документация&#xA; Центральный потенциал политики и направления, который рассматривает консолидированный профиль P &amp; L банка и производительности и определяет и направляет политики активов и обязательств. Также санкции и / или влияние на крупные сделки&#xA;&#xA;"/>
