<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Merchant Acquiring Facility"
    id="3ceaba48-37b1-4d45-9db8-8466421ab148"
    documentation="&#xA;&#xA;Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;The Acquiring Bank signs up Merchants for accepting Card Payments and opens Merchant Accounts for them. When Merchants submit card payment transactions, the Acquiring Bank is responsible for paying the Merchants in accordance with the terms of the Merchant agreement, which specify when the merchant should be paid and the amount that is withheld from the payment as merchant discount or service fees.&#xA;&#xA; General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain is the primary service domain for handling the Merchant Account and the specific terms and conditions for the merchant. It includes opening the Merchant account, preforming the required setup for card acceptance, such as assigning POS terminals, maintaining the accounts payable balances for the merchant, performing periodic settlement, and handling fees and charges. &#xA;++++++When Merchants submit card payment transactions, the Acquiring Bank is responsible for paying the Merchants in accordance with the terms of the Merchant agreement, which specify when the merchant should be paid and the amount that is withheld from the payment as merchant discount or service fees.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Orchestrate the activities related to Merchant fulfillment, Merchant Account maintenance, Merchant transactional activities and settlement, including the billing of merchant fees and charges.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Банк-эквайер регистрирует мерчантов для приема карточных платежей и открывает для них Мерчант-счета. Когда продавцы отправляют платежные операции по карте, банк-эквайер несет ответственность за оплату продавцов в соответствии с условиями торгового соглашения, в котором указывается, когда продавец должен быть оплачен, и сумма, которая удерживается из платежа в качестве торговой скидки или платы за услуги.&#xA;&#xA; Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен услуг является основным доменом услуг для обработки торгового счета и конкретных условий для продавца. Она включает в себя открытие Мерчант счета, предварительную настройку для приема карт, такую как назначение POS-терминалов, ведение кредиторской задолженности для мерчанта, выполнение периодических расчетов, а также обработку платежей и платежей.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Организовывать деятельность, связанную с исполнением Мерчанта, обслуживанием Мерчант аккаунта, транзакционной деятельностью Мерчанта и расчетами, включая выставление счетов за услуги мерчанта.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain orchestrates the activities related to Merchant fulfillment, Merchant Account maintenance, Merchant transactional activities and settlement, including the billing of merchant fees and charges&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;The Acquiring Bank signs up Merchants for accepting Card Payments and opens Merchant Accounts for them&#xA;"/>
