<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Servicing Order (OLD Customer Order ) "
    id="f38745b0-1f7b-4725-9dd8-46b126391400"
    documentation="#запрос клиента&#xA;&#xA;Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A customer changes address and requests all products and service arrangements are updated&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;The concept of a customer order introduces a distribution service that can span multiple products and services and may involve cycles and possibly fees/charges. There may be several types of 'order' type facility developed over time&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Handle the processing of a customer order or request&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент меняет адрес и запрашивает обновление всех продуктов и услуг&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Концепция заказа клиента вводит службу распространения, которая может охватывать несколько продуктов и услуг и может включать циклы и, возможно, сборы/платежи. Со временем может быть разработано несколько типов объектов типа &quot; заказ&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Обработка заказа или запроса клиента&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:&#xA; Handle the processing of a banking-services related request from a customer or a party representing a customer&#xA;&#xA;Example of use:&#xA;A customer changes address and requests the bank to update his records accordingly&#xA;General comment:&#xA;The concept of a servicing order introduces a distribution service that can span multiple products and services and may involve cycles and possibly incurs fees/charges. Servicing order typically orchestrates the origination part of handling a change on the bank's side. It is in many cases invoked by Contact Dialogue.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Servicing Order&#xA;The Servicing Order service domain handles the processing of a request that may impact multiple products and services and may involve processing cycles/steps and possibly have associated fees/charges. There can be several types of standard 'servicing order' defined for selection as appropriate. A servicing order can be initiated by a customer directly or may be requested on their behalf by an authorized third party service provider. If the request is made by a third party service provider on behalf of a customer the process can include a check that the associated permissions/mandates are in place&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain handles the processing of a customer servicing request as a predefined procedure. A range of standard servicing requests can be supported. The process can include a check of permissions when the request is made by a third party/service provider&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain handles the processing of a customer servicing request as a predefined procedure. A range of standard servicing requests can be supported. The process can include a check of permissions when the request is made by a third party/service provider&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A customer changes address and requests that all of their product and service arrangements are updated&#xA;"/>
