<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Offer"
    id="0461bbe6-1050-4d7a-9094-33629790e77a"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;An existing customer has discussed short term funding needs with the Financial Advisor and agree in principle to establish a corporate loan. The Offer Management process works through the detailed checks, authorizations and documentation needed prior to the Corporate Loan Service Domain establishing the new facility&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;The Offer Management Service Domain is general for all types of customers and any combination of product or service. It brings together product/service specific details (e.g. pricing &amp; negotiation ranges, documentation/authorization/regulatory requirements, eligibility and declarations, credit and other customer details), customer specific details (e.g. credit standing, other classifications such as operational overhead/retention target/activity history, demographics and segmentation) and orchestrates a potentially complex/multi-threaded workflow to get the offer to the point where the product/service can be initiated.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Orchestrate the processing of an offer for a new customer or an existing customer. The offer process it defined primarily my the nature of the product or service being considered, but can include actions such as document checks, collateral allocation, credit assessments, underwriting decisions, regulatory and procedural checks, eligibility checks, the use of internal and external specialist services (such as evaluations and legal advice).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Существующий клиент обсудил краткосрочные потребности в финансировании с финансовым консультантом и в принципе согласился на создание корпоративного кредита. Процесс управления предложением проходит тщательную проверку, авторизацию и документирование, необходимые до создания новой услуги корпоративного кредитования&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Домен службы Управления предложениями является общим для всех типов клиентов и любой комбинации продуктов или услуг. Он объединяет конкретные детали продукта / услуги (например, ценовые и переговорные диапазоны, документация / разрешение / нормативные требования, право и декларации, кредитные и другие детали клиента), конкретные детали клиента (например, кредитоспособности, других классификаций, таких как операционные накладные расходы/целевой удержания/история деятельности, демографические данные и сегментация) и организует потенциально сложный/многопоточный рабочий процесс, чтобы получить предложение до точки, где продукт/услуга может быть инициирована.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Организация обработки предложения для нового или существующего клиента. Процесс предложения он определял, прежде всего, мой характер рассматриваемого продукта или услуги, но может включать в себя такие действия, как проверка документов, распределение залога, оценка кредита, андеррайтинговые решения, нормативные и процедурные проверки, проверки соответствия требованиям, использование внутренних и внешних специализированных услуг (таких как оценки и юридические консультации).&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Customer Offer&#xA;The Offer Management Service Domain can process offers for all types of customers and any allowed combination of product or service. It references the Product Directory for the product specific offer instructions it must follow. The offer process may combine the selection of product/service specific details (e.g. pricing &amp; negotiation ranges, documentation/authorization/regulatory requirements, eligibility and declarations, credit and other customer details), customer specific details (e.g. credit standing, other classifications such as operational overhead/retention target/activity history, demographics and segmentation). The service domain orchestrates a potentially complex/multi-threaded/multi stage workflow to get the offer to the point where the product/service can be initiated.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain orchestrates the processing of a product offer for a new or established  customer. The offer process is defined specifically for the product or service being considered and can include actions such as document checks, collateral allocation, credit assessments, underwriting decisions, regulatory and procedural checks, eligibility checks, the use of internal and external specialist services (such as evaluations and legal advice).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain orchestrates the processing of a product offer for a new or established customer. The offer process is defined specifically for the product or service being considered and can include actions such as document checks, collateral allocation.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;An existing customer has discussed short term funding needs with the Financial Advisor and agreed in principle to taking out a corporate loan. The customer offer process is initiated and leads the advisor through the detailed checks.&#xA;"/>
