<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Card Collections"
    id="1c8059a7-7d2d-47b2-8ca5-65e069e43f47"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;A card account is canceled when the age of outstanding balance exceeds policy limits (normally 90 days) or when delinquency management and dunning efforts are determined to be unsuccessful at eliciting payment. The account is then assigned to an internal Collections department or an external Collection Agency for making aggressive attempts at securing the payment of the outstandings.&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;This service domain handles the determination and execution of the optimal strategy to ensure the collection of unsecured distressed card debt, which may include aggressive collection efforts, renegotiation of payments terms in order to improve customer commitment to make the payment, or to take any applicable legal actions against the customer.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Administer the recovery of outstanding amounts from cancelled card accounts through internal or external collection agencies. This may involve negotiating payment terms or interest write-down.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Карточный счет аннулируется, когда возраст непогашенного остатка превышает пределы политики (обычно 90 дней) или когда управление просрочки и усилия dunning определяются как неудачные при получении платежа. Затем эта учетная запись присваивается внутреннему отделу инкассо или внешнему Агентству по инкассо для осуществления агрессивных попыток обеспечить выплату выдающихся сумм.&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Данный домен услуг занимается определением и исполнением оптимальной стратегии по обеспечению взыскания необеспеченной проблемной карточной задолженности, которая может включать в себя агрессивные усилия по взысканию, пересмотр условий платежей с целью улучшения обязательств клиента по осуществлению платежа или принятие любых применимых юридических мер против клиента.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Администрирование взыскании суммы задолженности отменено карточных счетов через внутренние или внешние коллекторские агентства. Это может включать согласование условий оплаты или списание процентов.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Card Collections&#xA;The card collection process relates to the determination and execution of the optimal strategy to ensure the collection of unsecured distressed card debt, which may include aggressive collection efforts, renegotiation of payments terms in order to improve customer commitment to make the payment, or to take any applicable legal actions against the customer.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain administers the recovery of outstanding amounts from cancelled card accounts through internal or external collection agencies. This may involve negotiating payment terms and/or interest write-downs.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A card account is canceled when the age of outstanding balance exceeds policy limits or when delinquency management and dunning efforts are determined to be unsuccessful at eliciting payment.It is then assigned to an agency for making aggressive attempts at securing the payment of the outstandings."/>
