<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Counterparty Administration"
    id="6f1212b9-29b4-4d27-8718-fbb72ce9862c"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Back office clearing and settlement references the counterparty details to assemble a funds transfer as part of an equity trade using the counterparty details to generate the associated SWIFT based payment exchange&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;Counterparty Administration uses external feeds to maintain the counterparty details needed to support trading activity but can also provides the facility for specific terms/rules that can be applied selectively for a particular counterparty relationship. In more complex cases these terms may need to be captured as a specific counterparty agreement with an associated Service Domain where the changes have contractual significance&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Maintain and provide access to the counterparty reference details to support trading/payment activity. This includes SWIFT addresses, standard settlement instructions that are published. The data is typically acquired using a market feed for the default values, but the facility can support the maintenance of specific details and instructions that apply to the counterparty relationship overriding the public default&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиринг и расчеты бэк-офиса ссылаются на детали контрагента, чтобы собрать перевод средств в рамках торговли акциями, используя детали контрагента для создания связанного обмена платежами на основе SWIFT&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Администрация контрагента использует внешние каналы для ведения сведений о контрагенте, необходимых для поддержки торговой деятельности, но также может предоставить возможность для конкретных условий / правил, которые могут применяться выборочно для конкретных отношений с контрагентом. В более сложных случаях эти условия могут потребоваться в качестве отдельного соглашения контрагента со связанным доменом услуг, если изменения имеют договорное значение&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Поддерживать и предоставлять доступ к справочным данным контрагента для поддержки торговой / платежной деятельности. Сюда входят SWIFT адреса, стандартные расчетные инструкции, которые публикуются. Данные обычно получают с помощью рынка кормов для значения по умолчанию, но возможность установить содержание конкретных деталей и инструкции, которые относятся к взаимоотношениям контрагента переопределение по умолчанию"/>
