<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Product Deployment"
    id="15519ec9-4ec9-406c-9ad6-30bd21c34d6f"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A significant regulatory change mandates a revision of the terms of an existing product. An amended version is developed and the corresponding customer notification, internal training and production rollout is coordinated&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This is specific to the production acceptance, conversion, training and cutover for new and updated products and services. Note some banks will define and refine their own products, with highly specific features and pricing structures. The rollout time or 'time to money' for new and amended products is a key performance metric for banks active in highly competitive markets&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Plan and administer the deployment activities for new and enhanced products, includes training, inventory and solution deployment and coordination with operations, servicing, marketing and sales activities&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Значительное изменение в законодательстве требует пересмотра условий существующего продукта. Разрабатывается измененная версия и координируется соответствующее уведомление клиента, внутреннее обучение и развертывание производства&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Это специфически к принятию продукции, преобразованию, тренировке и cutover для новых и обновленных продуктов и обслуживаний. Обратите внимание, некоторые банки будут определять и совершенствовать свои продукты, с весьма специфическими особенностями и ценовой структуры. Время развертывания времени или денег для новых и измененных продуктов является ключевым показателем эффективности для банков, действующих на высококонкурентных рынках&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Планирование и администрирование мероприятий по развертыванию новых и усовершенствованных продуктов, включая обучение, инвентаризацию и развертывание решений, а также координацию с операциями, обслуживанием, маркетингом и продажами"/>
