<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Card Transaction Switch"
    id="89cf424b-074e-45ff-969e-6d5aee528111"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;An authorization request or sale transaction message is received from the Point of Sale device by the Acquiring Bank, which then needs to route the message to the Card Issuing Bank through the Card Network (e.g. Visa, MC, AMEX or Diners etc.), await the response from the Card Issuer and communicate it to the Merchant through the Point of Sale device.&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;This service domain handles the processing and asynchronous switching of Card Transaction related messages, such as Authorization, Sale, Void, Refund, etc. between the Acquiring Bank and the Issuing Bank through the Card Network. It has a role within the Acquiring Bank in switching transactions acquired from the Merchant to the Card Network, within the Card Network to switch the transaction to the applicable Card Issuer, and within the Card Issuer to switch the transaction to the instance of the Card Authorization service domain for the card product involved.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;Orchestrate the switching and routing of Card Authorization and Financial transactions received through the Card POS Network, Card E-Commerce Gateway, or the ATM Network from the Acquirer to the Issuer through the Card Networks.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Запрос на авторизацию или сообщение о сделке продажи поступает из точки продажи устройства банком-эквайером, который затем должен направить сообщение в банк-эмитент карты через сеть карт (например, Visa, MC, AMEX или Diners и т.д.), дождитесь ответа от эмитента карты и передайте его продавцу через точку продажи устройства.&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Этот домен обслуживания регулирует обрабатывать и асинхронное переключение сообщений карточки отнесенных Трудыами, как утверждение, сбывание, свободное пространство, возврат, etc. между банком-эквайером и Банком-эмитентом через сеть карт. Он играет важную роль в банк-эквайер в переключении операций, приобретенных от торговца к сети карточки, в карте сети для переключения операций применимому эмитента карты, и в карты эмитента для переключения сделки к экземпляру авторизации службы домена для карточки продукта.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Организовывать переключение и маршрутизацию авторизации карт и финансовых транзакций, полученных через сеть POS карт, шлюз электронной коммерции карт или сеть банкоматов от эквайера к эмитенту через сети карт.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Card Transaction Switch&#xA;This service domain handles the processing and asynchronous switching of Card Transaction related messages, such as Authorization, Sale, Void, Refund, etc. between the Acquiring Bank and the Issuing Bank through the Card Network. It has a role within the Acquiring Bank in switching transactions acquired from the Merchant to the Card Network, within the Card Network to switch the transaction to the applicable Card Issuer, and within the Card Issuer to switch the transaction to the instance of the Card Authorization service domain for the card product involved&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain orchestrates the switching and routing of Card Authorization and Financial transactions received through the Card POS Network, Card E-Commerce Gateway, or the ATM Network from the Acquirer to the Issuer through the Card Networks&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;An authorization request or sale transaction message is received from the POS device by the Acquiring Bank, which then needs to route the message to the Card Issuing Bank through the Card Network, await the response from the Card Issuer and communicate it to the Merchant through the POS device&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
