<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Financial Accounting"
    id="86b4ff16-8495-4603-9401-eba6d73342b2"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;The corporate financial reports are assembled to schedule for accounting and general reporting needs&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain handles the posting of business activity to the bank's financial accounts. These will typically be double entry ledgers and can include multiple levels of consolidation (sub-ledgers) The financial accounts conform to chart of accounts and appropriate GAP rules and are rolled up into the GL as part of the financial statements&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Financial booking of all business activity in an ledger/sub-ledger accounting structure/hierarchy according to the appropriate chart of accounts&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Корпоративные финансовые отчеты собираются в соответствии с графиком для нужд бухгалтерского учета и общей отчетности&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен услуг обрабатывает учет деловой активности на финансовых счетах банка. Как правило, это регистры двойной записи, они могут включать несколько уровней консолидации (субкниги). финансовые счета соответствуют плану счетов и соответствующим правилам разрыва и сворачиваются в ГК как часть финансовых отчетов&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;_Бух_проводки_ всей бизнес_деятельности в структуре/иерархии бухгалтерской книги/субкниги согласно соответствующему плану счетов&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Financial Accounting&#xA;This service domain handles the posting of business activity to the bank's financial accounts. These will typically be double entry ledgers and can include multiple levels of consolidation (sub-ledgers) The financial accounts conform to the bank's chart of accounts and appropriate GAP rules and are rolled up into the GL as part of the financial statements&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain handles financial booking of all business activity in a ledger/sub-ledger accounting structure/hierarchy according to the appropriate chart of accounts&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain handles financial booking of all business activity in a ledger/sub-ledger accounting structure/hierarchy according to the appropriate chart of accounts&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A business unit posts its financial transactions to the sub ledger at the end of the working day&#xA;"/>
