<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Collateral Allocation Management"
    id="6b91af93-c657-4d66-9a79-acc55193fc2b"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;A corporate applies for a new facility and the available collateral is checked to see if there is sufficient collateral on hand to allocate to the loan&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;This service domain manages the collateral holdings for a customer, in particular tracking and authorizing the allocation of collateral to different financial facilities. The service domain directs periodic valuation and oversees any collateral asset maintenance activity as needed. The service domain also provides reports on usage and make-up of the collateral - this can include applying specific analytical assessments to determine the value and liquidity across the range of collateral assets for broader risk management (e.g. when home properties are used as collateral, what is the right valuation ratio to apply based on market conditions)&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Administer the holding and allocation of collateral on behalf of a customer&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Корпоративный применяется для нового объекта и доступное обеспечение проверяется, чтобы увидеть, если есть достаточный залог под рукой, чтобы выделить кредит&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Эта область услуг управляет залоговыми активами клиента, в частности отслеживая и санкционируя распределение залога между различными финансовыми объектами. Область обслуживания направляет периодическую оценку и контролирует любую деятельность по обслуживанию залогового имущества по мере необходимости. Область услуг также предоставляет отчеты об использовании и составе обеспечения-это может включать применение конкретных аналитических оценок для определения стоимости и ликвидности по всему спектру залоговых активов для более широкого управления рисками (например когда домашняя недвижимость используется в качестве залога, каков правильный коэффициент оценки для применения на основе рыночных условий)&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Управление хранением и распределением залога от имени клиента&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Collateral Allocation Management&#xA;This service domain manages the collateral holdings for a customer, tracking and authorizing the allocation of collateral to different financial facilities. The service domain oversees periodic valuations and collateral asset maintenance activity as needed. The service domain also provides reports on overall collateral usage which can include applying specific analytical assessments to support general risk management (e.g. exposure to property value fluctuations based on prevailing market conditions)&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain manages the holding, valuation and allocation of a customer's collateral assets to products on behalf of a customer&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain manages the holding, valuation and allocation of a customer's collateral assets to products on behalf of a customer&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A corporate applies for a new facility and the available collateral is checked to see if there is sufficient collateral on hand to allocate to the loan&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
