<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Issued Device Tracking"
    id="435b3f41-e0b8-45e0-a676-e669f1853f6e"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Possible fraudulent activity is detected and the status of the card raised to watch to increase verification testing&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain tracks and reports on the state (e.g. valid date, usage, active status) for all issued devices. This covers credit/debit cards and can include other identification devices such as keychain fobs and in time will include virtual inventory such as electronic signatures and keys&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Tracks and report on the status of issued devices such as cards, fobs, etc issued to customers, including device cancellation&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Возможные мошеннические действия обнаружены и статус карточки, поднятые на часы, чтобы увеличить проверке &#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот сервисный домен отслеживает и сообщает о состоянии (например, действительная дата, использование, активный статус) для всех выпущенных устройств. Это покрывает кредитные / дебетовые карты и может включать в себя другие идентификационные устройства, такие как брелок для ключей и со временем будет включать в себя виртуальный инвентарь, такие как электронные подписи и ключи&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Отслеживание и доклад о состоянии выпущенных устройств, таких как карты, брелки и т. д., выданных клиентам, включая отмену устройство &#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Issued Device Tracking&#xA;This service domain tracks and reports on the state (e.g. suspended, flagged for possible fraud, cancelled) for all issued devices. This covers credit/debit cards and can include other identification devices such as keychain fobs and virtual authentication devices such as electronic signatures, passwords and keys. It may use an external service provider to obtain notifications and is responsible for providing notifications to external services when the bank detects problems with its own issued devices&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain handles operational access to issued device tracking services. Services report on the status of devices such as cards, fobs, etc. that have been issued to customers. Service notifications include fraud warnings/alerts and device cancellation.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A tracking service notifies the bank that one of its issued authentication devices has been detected in a fraudulent transaction. The bank suspends the device and initiates a fraud case to diagnose and resolve the situation.&#xA;"/>
