<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Relationship Management"
    id="17c6981e-a297-4809-877d-aca6a48c0f0a"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A corporate customer relationship manager reviews recent activity for a customer and notices that levels of activity are trending lower. Possible external (market) and internal (servicing/ fulfillment) activities are reviewed for possible causes. A meeting is scheduled to determine the reason and if any banking products/ services could help or are at further risk&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This function handles managed customer relationships. There can be a customer development plan and budget in more sophisticated implementations. The facility draws on external market insights and internal product and service fulfillment to track performance and sometimes trigger contact. The relationship manager can be a key source of business development providing a product/service matching and awareness role, is a single point of contact for sales and servicing channels, can help in issue resolution and trouble shooting. Relationship management applies to corporate and high net worth clients. More advanced automated knowledge based facilities can be considered for some relationship management functions at the consumer banking level, in particular for sales and marketing&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Develop, maintain and execute a customer plan to maintain and build a customer relationship. Activities include maintaining customer contact, tracking internal and external events and activity of interest and relevance, product and service matching and sales, processing ad-hoc queries, trouble shooting and issue resolution including the initial phases of troubled account recovery&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Менеджер по работе с корпоративными клиентами проверяет последние действия для клиента и замечает, что уровни активности имеют тенденцию ниже. Возможные внешние (рыночные) и внутренние (обслуживающие/ исполняющие) действия рассматриваются на предмет возможных причин. Встреча запланирована, чтобы определить причину, и если какие-либо банковские продукты/ услуги могут помочь или находятся под дальнейшим риском&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Эта функция обрабатывает управляемые отношения с клиентами. В более сложных реализациях может быть план развития клиента и бюджет. Объект опирается на внешние рыночные идеи и внутреннее выполнение продуктов и услуг для отслеживания производительности, а иногда и запуска контакта. Менеджер по взаимоотношениям может быть ключевым источником развития бизнеса, обеспечивающим соответствие продукта/услуги и роль осведомленности, является единой точкой контакта для каналов продаж и обслуживания, может помочь в разрешении проблем и устранении неполадок. Управление отношениями относится к корпоративным и состоятельным клиентам. Более продвинутые автоматизированные средства, основанные на знаниях, могут быть рассмотрены для некоторых функций управления отношениями на уровне банковского обслуживания потребителей, в частности для продаж и маркетинга&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Разработка, поддержка и выполнение плана клиента для поддержания и построения отношений с клиентом. Мероприятия включают в себя поддержание контакта с клиентами, отслеживание внутренних и внешних событий и деятельности, представляющих интерес и актуальность, соответствие продуктов и услуг и продаж, обработка специальных запросов, устранение неполадок и разрешение проблем, включая начальные фазы восстановления проблемной учетной записи&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Customer Relationship Management&#xA;This function handles managed customer relationships. There will typically be a customer development plan and budget/targets for higher value customers. The function may draw on external market insights as well as internal product and service fulfillment to track performance and trigger contact when appropriate. The function is a key source of business development providing product/service matching and awareness. As the primary point of contact the relationship manager can help in issue resolution and trouble shooting. Relationship management applies to corporate and high net-worth clients. Automated knowledge-based facilities may offer some relationship management functions at the consumer banking level in particular for sales and marketing.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain develops and executes a customer plan to maintain and build a customer relationship. Activities include ongoing customer contact, tracking internal and external events and activity of interest and relevance, product and service matching and sales, processing ad-hoc queries, trouble shooting and issue resolution including the initial phases of troubled account recovery.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain develops and executes a customer plan to maintain and build a customer relationship. Activities include ongoing customer contact, tracking internal and external events and activity of interest and relevance, product and service matching and sales, processing ad-hoc queries.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A corporate customer relationship manager reviews recent activity for a customer and notices that levels of activity are trending lower. Possible external (market) and internal (servicing/ fulfillment) activities are reviewed for possible causes.&#xA;"/>
