<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Product Quality Assurance"
    id="92197a91-9e5c-466a-abd8-cb20042ceca2"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A selection of response times and results are defined and applied to the sales and servicing support center for a newly launched product to determine if various performance goals are being achieved. Staff product specific training is adjusted and applied to address identified shortfalls&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This is the maintenance and execution of ongoing product and service quality assurance. It does not cover root cause analysis or procedural assurance/audit tasks nor customer surveys and reviews. It is specific (sample based) testing to ensure product and services are delivered to the prescribed performance levels and provides direct feedback to product specific training, operational support and product development capabilities&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Maintain and execute a portfolio of product quality assurance tests and if appropriate certifications. These tests can be applied to any specific aspects of product sales, servicing and fulfillment as might be appropriate&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Выбор времени отклика и результатов определяется и применяется к центру поддержки продаж и обслуживания для недавно запущенного продукта, чтобы определить, достигаются ли различные цели производительности. Обучение персонала по конкретным продуктам корректируется и применяется для устранения выявленных недостатков&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Это обслуживание и исполнение продолжающийся обеспечения качества продукта и обслуживания. Он не охватывает анализ основных причин или процедурные задачи обеспечения/аудита, а также опросы и обзоры клиентов. Это специфическое (на основе выборки) тестирование, чтобы гарантировать, что продукт и услуги поставляются на предписанные уровни производительности и обеспечивает прямую обратную связь с продуктом конкретного обучения, оперативной поддержки и возможностей разработки продукта&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Ведение и выполнение портфеля тестов по обеспечению качества продукции и, при необходимости, сертификаций. Эти тесты могут быть применены к любым конкретным аспектам продажи, обслуживания и выполнения продукта, которые могут быть целесообразными"/>
