<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Special Pricing Conditions"
    id="c7e59c44-67e8-4a12-b377-471058c41c37"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;A set of product agnostic special pricing conditions is assigned to a customer and stored in the SD Special Pricing Conditions Agreement. It will be considered for contracts of this customer which are stored in the SD Sales Product Agreements.&#xA;&#xA;New contract:&#xA;An established customer completes the application process (aka origination) for a new product and a new Sales Product Agreement is created to reflect the new business, considering the special pricing conditions which apply to this product.&#xA;The negotiation ranges for the conditions applied to this product are considered during the application process.&#xA;&#xA;Existing contracts:&#xA;The set of special pricing conditions which is assigned to a customer can be considered for all existing Sales Product Agreements which are affected by the special pricing conditions.&#xA;&#xA;General comments&#xA;Business rules are used which define whether and how the special pricing conditions apply to new and existing Sales Product Agreements.&#xA;&#xA;Capability&#xA;Maintain lifecycle of Special Pricing Conditions&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Maintain a price list or single conditions (with ranges and optional terms) by various dimensions, e.g. customer segment (e.g. employee conditions), for exceptional product independent pricing conditions that override standard pricing derived from the pricing product.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Набор не зависящих от продукта специальных условий ценообразования присваивается клиенту и хранится в соглашении SD специальные условия ценообразования. Он будет рассматриваться для контрактов этого клиента, которые хранятся в соглашениях о продаже продуктов SD.&#xA;&#xA;Новый контракт:&#xA;Установленный клиент завершает процесс подачи заявки (aka origination) для нового продукта, и создается новое соглашение о продаже продукта, чтобы отразить новый бизнес, учитывая специальные условия ценообразования, которые применяются к этому продукту.&#xA;Диапазоны согласования условий, применяемых к данному изделию, рассматриваются в процессе нанесения.&#xA;&#xA;Имеющиеся контракты:&#xA;Набор специальных условий ценообразования, назначенный клиенту, может быть рассмотрен для всех существующих договоров продажи продукции, на которые влияют специальные условия ценообразования.&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание&#xA;Бизнес-правила используются, которые определяют, применяются ли и как специальные условия ценообразования к новым и существующим соглашениям по продуктам продажи.&#xA;&#xA;Способность&#xA;Поддержание жизненного цикла специальных ценовых условий&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Ведение прайс-листа или отдельных условий (с диапазонами и необязательными условиями) по различным измерениям, например, сегмент клиента (например, условия для сотрудников), для исключительных независимых от продукта ценовых условий, которые переопределяют стандартное ценообразование, полученное из ценового продукта."/>
