<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Market Making"
    id="36dbbfe1-dd8b-4bef-857e-a0bcb84e1ea8"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A financial institution acts as the market maker for a number of market assets/securities. Buy and sell trades are automatically captured and the pricing adjusted to maintain a limited net position by influencing buy/sell decisions&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This trading capability supports the specific market activity of market making that is supported for certain market assets in certain exchanges. The market making facility has the ability to capture and execute buy and sell trades automatically and adjusts the price to balance sell and buy activity and avoid building a large net position. income is from the buy/sell spread and possibly aspects of trading fees depending on the market making arrangement&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Orchestrate the market making of a security (matching buy to sell orders typically through coordination with a stock exchange)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Финансовое учреждение выступает в качестве маркет-мейкера ряда рыночных активов / ценных бумаг. Сделки на покупку и продажу автоматически фиксируются, а цены корректируются для поддержания ограниченной чистой позиции, влияя на решения о покупке/продаже&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Эта торговая возможность поддерживает определенную рыночную активность создания рынка, которая поддерживается для определенных рыночных активов на определенных биржах. Механизм создания рынка имеет возможность захватывать и выполнять сделки на покупку и продажу автоматически и регулирует цену, чтобы сбалансировать продажу и покупку и избежать создания большой чистой позиции. доход от покупки / продажи спреда и, возможно, аспекты торговых сборов в зависимости от рыночной договоренности&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Организовывать создание рынка ценной бумаги (обычно путем согласования ордеров на покупку и продажу с фондовой биржей)&#xA;"/>
