<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Deposit Account"
    id="2675c34d-b78d-484f-ad41-36bebbde6b70"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A consumer customer establishes a sweep facility from their current account to a savings deposit facility to obtain a higher interest rate&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;Consumer deposits are captured here as a financial facility, representing it as a persistent service with potentially many payment and withdrawal transactions over the term of the facility. There can be specific consumer deposit 'instruments' (e.g. CDs) which may justify a different service domain for their fulfillment as they are more transactional in their behavior. Many of these can be covered under the Investments business area&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Orchestrate the different flavors of a consumer deposit accounting facilities (including savings, term or demand) including the handling of associated services and fees&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Потребительский клиент устанавливает средство развертки со своего текущего счета на сберегательный депозит, чтобы получить более высокую процентную ставку&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Потребительские депозиты учитываются здесь как финансовый объект, представляя его как постоянную услугу с потенциально большим количеством транзакций платежей и снятия средств в течение срока действия объекта. Могут быть определенные потребительские депозитные &quot;инструменты&quot; (например, CDs), которые могут оправдывать другую область обслуживания для их выполнения, поскольку они более транзакционны в своем поведении. Многие из них могут быть охвачены инвестиционной сферой бизнеса&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Организовать различные варианты средств учета вкладов потребителей (включая сбережения, срок или спрос), включая обработку связанных с ними услуг и сборов&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain handles the set-up and fulfillment of consumer fixed term deposits including the handling of all associated services and fees&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A consumer customer establishes a term deposit in order to obtain a higher interest rate for excess funds they do not anticipate needing over the term of the deposit&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Deposit Account&#xA;The consumer term deposit is a financial facility that may provide limited access for interim/early withdrawals and terminations which will carry associated fees and penalties. Interest is accrued over the term of the deposit which can usually be rolled over at maturity&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
