<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Contact Handler"
    id="5cfdbaa4-3a1d-4f97-901f-3979b4a588aa"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A customer is self serving on the web and then requests to talk to a rep using the VoIP capability&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;The way a customer interaction is captured in BIAN defines a contact as the overarching structure that may include one or more sessions in parallel or sequence to support different device/channel uses within the contact and to allow for the customer to be passed on to different specialists as necessary. Contact Handler concludes the contact and handles any shared authorization and activity data between sessions as necessary&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Handle the customer interactive contact, including the launching of one or more channel/device specific sessions as necessary within the contact&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент сам обслуживает в интернете, а затем просит поговорить с представителем, используя возможность VoIP&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Способ взаимодействия с клиентом в BIAN определяет контакт как всеобъемлющую структуру, которая может включать в себя один или несколько сеансов параллельно или последовательно для поддержки различных устройств/каналов использования в Контакте и позволяет клиенту быть переданы различным специалистам по мере необходимости. Обработчик контактов завершает контакт и при необходимости обрабатывает данные авторизации и действия, совместно используемые сеансами&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Обработка интерактивного контакта с клиентом, включая запуск одного или нескольких сеансов канала/устройства в контакте по мере необходимости&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Contact Handler&#xA;BIAN defines a customer contact as the overarching structure handling a customer interaction from start to end. A contact can include one or more servicing dialogue 'sessions' in parallel or sequence to support different device/channel uses within the contact and to allow for the customer to be passed on to different servicing specialists as necessary during the contact. Each session is handled at a servicing position where the Contact Dialogue service domain is called to handle the specific customer interaction. Contact Handler concludes the contact, handles the authorization permissions and shares any contact information collected during the contact between sessions as necessary&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain handles a customer's interactive contact with the bank. This will typically involve launching of one or more channel/device specific dialogue sessions as necessary within the customer contact&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain handles a customer's interactive contact with the bank. This will typically involve launching of one or more channel/device specific dialogue sessions as necessary within the customer contact&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A customer is self serving on the web and then requests to talk to a servicing representative directory using the VoIP capability presented on the banks web portal&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
