<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Corporate Treasury"
    id="64b39361-2f67-4fa1-b937-2c0d23e56dc5"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;The Bank Treasury consolidates trading and lending activity across its corporate clients to develop timely views of current positions and maturity projections&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain manages and administers the consolidation of transaction details and summaries in order to derive and report on the array of consolidated positions managed by Treasury. This includes the assembly of related maturity ladders (cash flow projections)&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Orchestrate the consolidation and presentation of summary transaction details in order to assemble a timely and accurate view of the overall treasury position of the Bank at any one time&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Казначейство банка консолидирует торговую и кредитную деятельность по всем корпоративным клиентам для своевременной оценки текущих позиций и прогнозирования сроков погашения&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен услуг управляет и администрирует консолидацию сведений о транзакциях и сводок, чтобы получить и сообщить о массиве консолидированных позиций, управляемых Казначейством. Это включает в себя сборку соответствующих лестниц зрелости (прогноз движения денежных средств)&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Организовывать консолидацию и представление кратких сведений о транзакциях с целью получения своевременного и точного представления общей казначейской позиции банка в любой момент времени.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Corporate Treasury&#xA;This service domain manages and administers the consolidation of transaction details and summaries in order to derive and report on the array of consolidated positions managed by Treasury. This includes the assembly of related maturity ladders (cash flow projections) and managing tactical and strategic funding activity for the bank. It is also responsible for tracking prevailing market conditions and determining the various bank rates that should be applied throughout the bank.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain orchestrates the consolidation and presentation of summary transaction details in order to assemble a timely and accurate view of the overall treasury position of the Bank at any one time. It is also responsible for determining the different interest and exchange rates applied to different products and services within the bank.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain orchestrates the consolidation and presentation of summary transaction details in order to assemble a timely and accurate view of the overall treasury position of the Bank at any one time.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;The Bank Treasury consolidates trading and lending activity across its corporate clients to develop timely views of current positions and maturity projections."/>
