<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Point of Service"
    id="10c24ae9-e157-46eb-b6aa-c95b22fd87dc"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Teller personnel are assigned to teller positions where they are provided with a cash float and consumer product application access. The support system logs activity that is captured for activity and root cause analysis&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;The servicing position supports all point of sale and channel based customer activity including tellers and contact center positions. The facility provides access to application based utilities, activity tracking and production application access as necessary. It can include CTI if appropriate. The service domain integrates the use of Customer Dialogue for narrative handling when appropriate&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Administer all media connections (channel and application), inventory holdings (e.g. cash) provide support utilities and track activity at a servicing position - time spent, log activity, capture servicing events including commission and training related activities.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Персонал кассира назначается на должности кассира, где ему предоставляется доступ к денежному переводу и приложению потребительских товаров. Система поддержки регистрирует действия, записанные для анализа активности и основных причин&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Позиция обслуживания поддерживает все точки продаж и канал на основе активности клиентов, включая кассиров и контакт-центр позиции. Объект обеспечивает доступ к утилитам на основе приложений, отслеживание активности и доступ к производственным приложениям по мере необходимости. Это может включать CTI при необходимости. Домен обслуживания интегрирует использование диалога клиента для повествовательной обработки, когда это необходимо&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Администрировать все медиа соединения (канал и приложения), запасы (например, денежные средства) обеспечивают поддержку коммунальных услуг и отслеживать деятельность на обслуживание позиции - время, проведенное, войти деятельность, захват события обслуживания, включая комиссии и обучения, связанных с деятельностью.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Point Of Service&#xA;The servicing position supports all point of sale, branch and channel based customer interactions including e-tellers and contact/service center positions. The facility provides access to product and service systems, supports activity tracking and access to other support and administrative systems as necessary. It can include CTI as appropriate. The service domain integrates with the Customer Dialogue service domain for customer session/narrative support when appropriate. The servicing position can be fully automated for some servicing activities&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain operates servicing positions within the bank. It administers all media connections, inventory holdings (e.g. cash), provides access to support utilities and tracks servicing activity -e.g. time spent, activity logs, capturing servicing events including commission and training related actions. In cases servicing positions can be automated&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain operates servicing positions within the bank. It administers all media connections, inventory holdings, provides access to support utilities and tracks servicing activity. In cases servicing positions can be automated&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;Teller personnel are assigned to teller servicing positions at a branch where they are provided with a cash float and access to consumer product support systems"/>
