<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Agreement"
    id="9f59ee59-82b5-4f0f-a2f9-143a56f64375"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;An new customer agreement is established prior to setting up product specific agreements&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;The Customer Agreement captures the legal terms of conditions in force for a customer (which as noted can be a complex multinational).&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Maintains the details of the products services and channel access that the customer has in place. This profile is referenced in servicing and fulfillment activity. The view may also be compared to the full range of eligible products and services to identify business development opportunities.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Новое соглашение с клиентом устанавливается до создания соглашений по конкретным продуктам&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Клиентское соглашение отражает юридические условия, действующие для клиента (которые, как отмечалось, могут быть сложными многонациональными).&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;&#xA;: Поддерживает детали обслуживаний продуктов и доступа канала который клиент имеет в_текущий_момент. На этот профиль ссылаются в действии обслуживания и выполнения. Это мнение можно также сравнить с полным спектром приемлемых продуктов и услуг для определения возможностей развития бизнеса.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Customer Agreement&#xA;The Customer Agreement service domain captures and maintains the master legal terms of conditions in force for a customer (which as noted can be a complex multinational with many underlying product and service specific agreements).&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains the master customer agreement/legal contract. Note that a customer can be a complex corporate entity with many subsidiaries operating in different geopolitical areas. The customer agreement is linked to as many Sales Product Agreements as needed for all in-force products.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains the master customer agreement/legal contract. Note that a customer can be a complex corporate entity with many subsidiaries operating in different geopolitical areas. The customer agreement is linked to as many Sales Product Agreements as needed for all in-force product&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;An new customer's master agreement is established prior to negotiating and setting up the underlying product specific agreements.&#xA;&#xA;"/>
