<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Servicing Issue"
    id="67c1c076-13b2-40f4-a68b-65364092a08c"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A customer requests that the CSR arranges for marketing materials to be sent out - an action for which no standard case processing is available&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;The service domain is used for the capture and resolution of issues that arise that can not be resolved completely during a customer contact or classified as customer cases for which a formal case specific process is initiated. Servicing issues could be out of pattern customer requests/notifications or processing errors that the CSR needs to follow up (such as missed commission claims or captured customer insights). Some implementations will not allow for any non-standard case follow up scenarios&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;&#xA; Capture, track, resolve and report on customer servicing issues - note this excludes contacts that are resolved and cases that are raised. Issues are actions requiring some kind of follow-up by the contact service representative (CSR)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент запрашивает, чтобы CSR организовал отправку маркетинговых материалов-действие, для которого недоступна стандартная обработка обращений&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Домен обслуживания используется для отслеживания и разрешения проблем, которые не могут быть решены полностью во время контакта с клиентом или классифицированы как случаи клиента, для которых инициируется процесс формального конкретного случая. Проблемы обслуживания могут быть вызваны нестандартными запросами/уведомлениями клиентов или ошибками обработки, которые CSR должен отслеживать (например, пропущенные комиссионные требования или полученные сведения о клиентах). Некоторые реализации не позволяют использовать нестандартные сценарии последующих действий&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;Захват, отслеживание, разрешение и отчет о проблемах обслуживания клиентов-обратите внимание, что это исключает контакты, которые разрешены и случаи, которые возникают. Вопросы, требующие контакта с CSR"/>
