<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Fraud Models"
    id="71a1b072-24bd-413d-8d84-3b83942b389b"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Financial engineers develop and refine a portfolio of fraud scanner and detection models for deployment across the bank&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain handles the development and deployment of fraud detection capabilities - fraud activity scanner and analyzers that are executed in the production environment to detect possible fraudulent activity as it occurs and after the event&#xA;++++This service domain handles the development and deployment of fraud detection capabilities. Fraud activity tests and analyzers are executed in the production environment in real time to detect possible fraudulent activity as it occurs and also using historical data to detect fraud after the event&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Develop and maintain a portfolio of fraud detection models and scanners. Support the use of these models in different production contexts and refine the models in response to new and changing exposures&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Финансовые инженеры разрабатывают и совершенствуют портфель сканеров мошенничества и моделей обнаружения для развертывания по всему банку&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен услуг занимается разработкой и развертыванием возможностей обнаружения мошенничества-сканеров и анализаторов мошеннических действий, которые выполняются в рабочей среде для обнаружения возможных мошеннических действий по мере их возникновения и после события&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Разработка и ведение портфеля моделей и сканеров для обнаружения мошенничества. Поддержка использования этих моделей в различных производственных контекстах и совершенствование моделей в ответ на новые и изменяющиеся воздействия&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain develops and maintains a portfolio of fraud detection models. It support the use of these models in different production contexts and refines the models in response to new and changing exposures&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;Financial engineers develop and refine a portfolio of fraud scanner and detection models for deployment across the bank&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Fraud Models&#xA;This service domain handles the development and deployment of fraud detection capabilities. Fraud activity tests and analyzers are executed in the production environment in real time to detect possible fraudulent activity as it occurs and also using historical data to detect fraud after the event&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;&#xA;This service domain develops and maintains a portfolio of fraud detection models. It support the use of these models in different production contexts and refines the models in response to new and changing exposures&#xA;"/>
