<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Payments Execution"
    id="34eabdca-5f1b-43b6-92a4-8a22ae186844"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Transfer funds from a customer account with the bank to an account with another bank&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;Payment Execution handles the bank side of a payment, the movement of money from debtor account to creditor account. Payments need to be authorised and validated against customer agreements, before being issued to Payment Execution. Payment Execution figures out whether debtor and creditor accounts are on-us, selecting the appropriate payment mechanism to reach these if not. It delegates the actual creation of debit and credit entries to Position Keeping.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Orchestrate the execution of payments between accounts within the bank or with other banks, selecting the appropriate payment mechanism&#xA;&#xA;Documentation&#xA; Orchestrate the execution of payment transactions, with, and between bank using any appropriate payment mechanism (A/C, wire, ACH)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Перевод средств со счета клиента в банке на счет в другом банке&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Исполнение платежа обрабатывает банковскую сторону платежа, движение денег со счета должника на счет кредитора. Выплаты должны быть уполномочены и проверка договоров с клиентами, перед отправкой платежа. Выполнение платежа выясняет, находятся ли счета должника и кредитора на нас, выбирая соответствующий механизм оплаты, чтобы достичь их, если нет. Он делегирует фактическое создание дебетовых и кредитовых проводок в ведение позиции.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Организовывать выполнение платежей между счетами в банке или в других банках, выбирая соответствующий механизм оплаты&#xA;&#xA;Документация&#xA; Организовывать выполнение платежных операций, с и между банком, используя любой соответствующий механизм оплаты (A/C, wire, ACH)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Payment Execution&#xA;Payment Execution handles the back-end processing of a movement funds from a debtor account to a creditor account. Payments need to have been authorized and validated against customer/bank agreements before being instructed to Payment Execution. Payment Execution then determines whether debtor and creditor accounts are held within the bank and if not selects the appropriate payment mechanism/channel to use to complete the transfer. It is responsible for ensuring that both (or neither) sides of the exchange are completed successfully&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domains processes the movement of funds between accounts within the bank or to/from an account held with another bank, selecting the appropriate payment mechanism&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;Funds are transferred from a customer's account with the bank to a payee account held at another bank&#xA;"/>
