<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Profile"
    id="8942b435-a50e-40c2-bc1a-1304098ed833"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;The identity and active status of a customer is checked as they present themselves on-line to access their bank account&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;The role of this service domain will be ratified in later versions of the landscape&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Maintain a small amount of current customer status data to identify and influence any real-time operational interaction for sales, servicing and/or fulfillment (e.g. high value, eligible for campaign, account suspended, open Case)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Личность и активный статус клиента проверяется, как они представляют себя в интернете, чтобы получить доступ к своему банковскому счету&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Роль этого домена услуг будет утверждена в более поздних версиях ландшафта&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Поддерживать небольшой объем текущих данных о состоянии клиентов, чтобы идентифицировать и влиять на любое оперативное взаимодействие в режиме реального времени для продаж, обслуживания и/или выполнения (например, высокая стоимость, право на кампанию, приостановленный счет, открытое дело)&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Customer Profile&#xA;The customer profile service domain is used to tune the customer experience during any real-time interaction with the bank. A collection of status indicators, ratings and alerts can be maintained that are then used to influence the routing and servicing decisions that govern the customer interaction. For example a status indicator could include a warning that the account is in distress which would limit sales activity and might result in routing a contact to a specialist account recovery servicing facility&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains a small profile of key indicators for a customer that is referenced during customer interactions to facilitate routing, servicing and product/service fulfillment decisions. This can include status (such as account in arrears), ratings (such as high value customer) and alerts (such possible fraud activity detected)&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains a small profile of key indicators for a customer that is referenced during customer interactions to facilitate routing, servicing and product/service fulfillment decisions. This can include status, ratings and alerts&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;The identity and active status of a customer is checked as they present themselves on-line to access their bank account"/>
