<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Financial Instrument Reference Data Management"
    id="0ff72a9a-1799-4a76-b319-7eaa550d3766"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A corporate financial advisory project references different instrument specifications when assembling a structured financial approach to the customer financing needs&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain maintains a master reference directory of all traded market asset details. For equity related assets this can include handling changes that results from corporate events such as stock splits where the implications go beyond updating the reference details. The service domain obtains market asset/instrument details from subscription market feeds and possibly other market intelligence sources. Features to ensure reference data integrity and process more complex asset related events could require additional Service Domains&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Maintain a central reference directory of market traded asset/instrument details. The details are typically captured from one or more market feeds that publish market asset/instrument details but can include handling necessary internal processing in response to reported corporate events such as stock splits that impact the asset beyond simply updating the reference details&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Корпоративный финансовый консультативный проект ссылается на различные спецификации инструментов при сборке структурированного финансового подхода к потребностям финансирования клиентов&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен услуг поддерживает основной справочник всех торгуемых рыночных активов. Для активов, связанных с капиталом, это может включать обработку изменений, которые являются результатом корпоративных событий, таких как разделение акций, когда последствия выходят за рамки обновления справочных данных. Домен услуг получает информацию о рыночных активах/инструментах из каналов подписки и, возможно, из других источников рыночной информации. Функции для обеспечения целостности справочных данных и обработки более сложных событий, связанных с активами, могут потребовать дополнительных доменов обслуживания&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Ведение Центрального справочника рыночных торгуемых активов/инструментов. Детали, как правило, захватываются из одного или нескольких каналов рынка, которые публикуют рыночные активы / детали инструмента, но может включать в себя обработку необходимой внутренней обработки в ответ на сообщенные корпоративные события, такие как расколы акций, которые влияют на актив, помимо простого обновления справочных данных"/>
