<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Market Data Switch Administration"
    id="1ee1d6eb-728c-4e9e-951d-1bc3cabcc9ec"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A new employee is provided with the standard access to information feed at their trading desk&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This is an internal data/page management capability for external data feeds and optionally formatted internally published information 'pages'. It is specific to trading type activity where a trader will configure a collection market new/analysis/price/trading related feeds to support the deal formulation activity. Note that the nature and relevance of this Service Domain is channel specific and may evolve with changes in market information dissemination practices&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Administer the internal information distribution 'switch' with external and external market information feeds and associated employee access rights. Note this can include 'brokering' information access on a first come first serve basis for limited active user number feed services&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Новому сотруднику предоставляется стандартный доступ к информационной ленте на своем торговом столе&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Это внутренняя возможность управления данными/страницами для внешних каналов данных и, возможно, отформатированных внутренних опубликованных информационных &quot;страниц&quot;. Это зависит от типа торговой деятельности, когда трейдер настроит коллекцию рынок новых/анализ/цена/торговая обзоры для поддержки разработки интернет-активности. Обратите внимание, что характер и релевантность этого домена услуг зависит от канала и может изменяться с изменениями в практике распространения рыночной информации&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Администрирование внутреннего информационного коммутатора с внешними и внешними информационными каналами рынка и соответствующими правами доступа сотрудников. Примечание это может включать минимальное время доступа к информации на первый пришел первый обслужен основе для ограниченного количества активных пользователей услуг корма &#xA;"/>
