<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Credit Rating"
    id="329a9c3a-2342-42cb-844a-7816e7564cbe"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A customer calls the contact center wishing to know what mortgage offers they are eligible for. The customer servicing representative (CSR) uses the customer's internal credit grade as input into the product matching utility to see what price range would apply&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain handles the derivation and maintenance of each customers credit rating, including consumer and corporate customers. The internal rating can integrate externally provided credit details from credit scoring agencies with internal transactional data and relationship assessments. The credit rating will be maintained based on internal rules, but it is possible that a service will be offered to support an unscheduled recalculation of the credit score&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Maintain and administer the credit scoring for customers based on consolidated internal data and optionally referencing external credit agency insights&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент звонит в контактный центр, чтобы узнать, на какие ипотечные предложения он имеет право. Представитель по обслуживанию клиентов (CSR) использует внутреннюю кредитную оценку клиента в качестве входных данных в утилите сопоставления продуктов, чтобы узнать, какой ценовой диапазон будет применяться&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Эта область обслуживания обрабатывает вывод и обслуживание каждого кредитного рейтинга клиентов, включая потребителей и корпоративных клиентов. Внутренний рейтинг может интегрировать предоставленные извне кредитные данные от агентств кредитного скоринга с внутренними транзакционными данными и оценками отношений. Кредитный рейтинг будет поддерживаться на основе внутренних правил, но не исключено, что будет предложена услуга по поддержке внепланового пересчета кредитного балла&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Ведение и администрирование кредитного скоринга для клиентов на основе консолидированных внутренних данных и, при необходимости, ссылок на инсайты внешних кредитных агентств.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Customer Credit Rating&#xA;This service domain handles the derivation and maintenance of each customer's credit rating for both consumer and corporate customers. The internal rating can integrate externally provided credit details from credit scoring agencies with internal transactional data and relationship assessments. The credit rating will be maintained based on internal rules, but it is possible that a service will be offered to support an unscheduled recalculation of the credit score.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains and administers the bank's credit assessment for customers based on consolidated internal data and optionally by referencing external credit agency reports.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains and administers the bank's credit assessment for customers based on consolidated internal data and optionally by referencing external credit agency reports&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A customer calls the contact center wishing to know what mortgage offers they are eligible for. The customer servicing representative (CSR) uses the customer's internal credit assessment as one input to reference the Product Directory to retrieve the details of available products and terms.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
