<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Regulatory Reporting"
    id="4ae63177-b891-4411-89d5-e99b747183ae"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Trading activity is reported to the exchange to comply with regulatory reporting requirements&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This includes the consolidation and presentation of information in regulatory reports and disclosures and handling the response to regulatory requests for information as part of ongoing relations, It also handles the scheduled consolidation, formatting and delivery of the range of compliance reports including 'on-line' trade reporting and after the event transaction analysis reporting&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Administer and orchestrate the required regulatory reporting schedule of regulatory reports&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Торговая деятельность сообщается бирже для соблюдения нормативных требований к отчетности&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Это включает консолидации и представления информации в отчетности и раскрытие информации и обращение на ответ в нормативно-запросы о предоставлении информации в рамках текущих отношений, он также выполняет запланированное объединение, форматирование и доставка диапазон соответствия отчетов, в том числе по линии торгово отчетности и после операции анализ отчетности&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Администрирование и организация требуемого регламентационного графика представления регламентационных отчетов&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Regulatory Reporting&#xA;The service domain handles the bank's regulatory reporting obligations. This includes the consolidation and presentation of information in regulatory reports and disclosures and handling the response to regulatory requests for information as part of ongoing regulator relations. It also handles the scheduled consolidation, formatting and delivery of the range of compliance reports including 'on-line' trade reporting and after the event transaction analysis reporting.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain administers and orchestrates the tasks required to meet the bank's regulatory reporting obligations.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains the master customer agreement/legal contract. Note that a customer can be a complex corporate entity with many subsidiaries operating in different geopolitical areas. The customer agreement is linked to as many Sales Product Agreements as needed for all in-force product&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;Trading activity is reported to the exchange to comply with regulatory reporting requirements&#xA;"/>
