<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Brokered Product"
    id="7debc112-5232-4122-b6e5-5831987a71fc"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Access to insurance brokers for branch customer is administered by teller and relationship management personnel&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain provides the day to day oversight and coordination of 3rd party product delivery. Orchestrating the involvement and activities with the 3rd party product/service supplier as necessary and troubleshooting issues as they arise. This activity is governed by 3rd party agreements. This simple capability supports basic brokerage product service/product support through any appropriate channel. Note that some financial institutions will incorporate complex and extensive brokerage activity for which a more sophisticated collection of service domains might be required&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Administer any 3rd party coordination with brokered products and service supplied through any bank channel&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Доступ к страховым брокерам для клиентов филиала осуществляется кассиром и персоналом по управлению отношениями&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен обеспечивает изо дня в день надзора и координации 3-й партии поставки товара. Организация участия и действий со сторонним поставщиком продуктов/услуг по мере необходимости и устранение проблем по мере их возникновения. Эта деятельность регулируется соглашениями третьих сторон. Эта простая возможность поддерживает базовое брокерское обслуживание продукта/поддержку продукта через любой соответствующий канал. Обратите внимание, что некоторые финансовые учреждения будут включать сложную и обширную брокерскую деятельность, для которой может потребоваться более сложный набор доменов обслуживания&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Администрировать любую координацию третьей стороны с брокерскими продуктами и услугами, поставляемыми через любой банковский канал&#xA;"/>
