<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Product Matching"
    id="154c9b03-ad50-474e-a5b4-9c4df749194a"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A corporate customer relationship manager provides general advice to a customer seeking to invest a short term cash excess. The manager uses customer details and product features to isolate the most appropriate product&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This function provides an interactive mapping of available products (and product combinations) to a customer based on customer type/characteristics, the context for the request and desired product/service features. The matching mechanism can prompt for additional details as may be necessary to isolate a product and/or confirm the eligibility of the customer for a specific product and/or associated terms and pricing levels. A more sophisticated matching capability can be sensitive to other factors such as business preferences/strategy and prevailing business/market conditions when selecting products to maximize sales, relationship and product profitability and influence customer retention&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Typically an interactive capability used to match available product and product combinations to a customer type and situation. The mapping logic can be responsive to more dynamic factors such as prevailing business conditions&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Менеджер по работе с корпоративными клиентами предоставляет общие консультации клиентам, стремящимся инвестировать краткосрочные денежные излишки. Менеджер использует сведения о клиенте и функции продукта, чтобы изолировать наиболее подходящий продукт&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Эта функция обеспечивает интерактивное сопоставление доступных продуктов (и комбинаций продуктов) с клиентом на основе типа/характеристик клиента, контекста запроса и требуемых функций продукта/услуги. Механизм сопоставления может запрашивать дополнительные сведения, которые могут потребоваться для изоляции продукта и/или подтверждения соответствия клиента конкретному продукту и/или связанным условиям и уровням цен. Более сложные возможности сопоставления могут быть чувствительны к другим факторам, таким как бизнес-предпочтения / стратегия и преобладающие бизнес / рыночные условия при выборе продуктов для максимизации продаж, отношений и рентабельности продукта и влияния на удержание клиентов&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Обычно интерактивная возможность, используемая для сопоставления доступных комбинаций продуктов и продуктов с типом и ситуацией клиента. Логика сопоставления может реагировать на более динамичные факторы, такие как преобладающие бизнес-условия&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Product Matching&#xA;This function provides an interactive match of available products (and product combinations) to a customer based on customer type/characteristics, the context for the request and desired product/service features. The matching mechanism can prompt for additional details as may be necessary to select a product and/or confirm the eligibility of the customer. The facility can also consider broader factors such as business preferences/strategy and prevailing business/market conditions when selecting products. Product Matching references the Customer Product/Service Eligibility service domain where the customer's use and eligibility to the bank's full range of products and services is maintained in order to limit the matching to only those products for which the customer is entitled and not already using&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;The Product Matching service domain matches available product and product combinations to a customer based on various factors. The factors include the type of product of interest, the context (e.g. customer request, relationship review, retention action, cross/up sell). The matching selection may also be influenced by broader bank priorities and policies that can change with prevailing business conditions&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;Matches available product and product combinations to a customer based on various factors. The factors include the type of product of interest, the context. The matching selection may also be influenced by broader bank priorities and policies that can change with prevailing business conditions&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A corporate customer relationship manager provides general advice to a customer seeking to invest a short term cash excess. The manager provides customer details and required product features to enable product matching to suggest the most appropriate product&#xA;"/>
