<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Interactive Help"
    id="2f0d9874-a11f-4fad-9b7c-059b42395307"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A customer logs in to set up the reporting option on their current account facility including enabling various on-line options. Rather than get CSR support, the customer reads through the context specific guidelines and self services the set-up. The new details are captured for subsequent authorization/ release&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;Interactive help is a service to provide on-line context specific guidance, typically for any machine assisted activity. It can help reduce training overheads and ensure operational consistency by providing clear and succinct guidance that is directly relevant to the task at hand. Interactive help is particularly useful in areas where there is constant change, such as active sales/campaigns or where often quite simple but extensive information is handled such as product specifications/rules. It is also a powerful lever to support self service when the guidance can be pitched for customers rather than specialist members of the workforce. Interactive help should be available cross channel and media and the access/use of interactive help should be tracked to provide additional insight into root cause analysis&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Provide Employee or Customer interactive context sensitive guidance&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент входит в систему, чтобы настроить опцию отчетности по их текущему счету, включая включение различных Он-лайн опций. Вместо того, чтобы получить поддержку КСО, клиент читает через контекст конкретных руководящих принципов и самообслуживания настройки. Новые сведения записываются для последующей авторизации / выпуска&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Интерактивная справка-это служба, предоставляющая интерактивные контекстные рекомендации, как правило, для любых действий, выполняемых с помощью компьютера. Это может помочь сократить накладные расходы на обучение и обеспечить оперативную согласованность путем предоставления четких и кратких указаний, которые имеют непосредственное отношение к поставленной задаче. Интерактивная справка особенно полезна в областях, где происходят постоянные изменения, таких как активные продажи/кампании или где часто обрабатывается довольно простая, но обширная информация, такая как спецификации/правила продукта. Это также сильный рычаг для того чтобы поддержать самообслуживание когда наведение можно соорудить для клиентов а не члены специалиста рабочей силы. Интерактивная справка должна быть доступна через канал и средства массовой информации и доступ / использование интерактивной справки следует отслеживать, чтобы обеспечить дополнительное понимание анализа первопричин&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Предоставление сотрудникам или клиентам интерактивных контекстно-зависимых рекомендаций"/>
