<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Letter of Credit"
    id="41afbe48-d904-4c48-b9ed-6ba77ef881ca"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;An LC is raised to support a large international trade deal&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain handles the pricing and issuance of a letter of credit, typically associated with corporate trading activity supported by a trade finance line of credit. In a full implementation additional service domains will be required to handle bank guarantees (correspondent banking), the complex trade finance transaction processing capabilities (national and international). Also there can be significant activity associated with trading letters of credit that can be modeled as an instrument handled by existing trading service domains or a specialized activity with its own service domains&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Orchestrate the pricing and issuance of Letters of Credit (typically associated with trade finance activity)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;LC поднимается для поддержки крупной международной торговой сделки&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен услуг управляет ценообразованием и выпуском аккредитива, обычно связанного с корпоративной торговой деятельностью, поддерживаемой кредитной линией торгового финансирования. При полной реализации потребуются дополнительные сервисные домены для обработки банковских гарантий (корреспондентские банковские операции), комплексные возможности обработки торговых финансовых операций (национальные и международные). Также может иметь место значительная активность, связанная с торговыми аккредитивами, которые могут быть смоделированы как инструмент, обрабатываемый существующими торговыми доменами услуг или специализированной деятельностью с собственными доменами услуг&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Организация ценообразования и выпуска аккредитивов (обычно связанных с деятельностью по торговому финансированию)&#xA;&#xA;"/>
