<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Issued Device Administration"
    id="bfffa8a5-7404-4230-81e6-f32f4e37e4a7"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A card is cancelled and a replacement card is generated and issued for a customer reporting a stolen card&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain administers the inventory management and allocation/issuance for all issued devices and materials (e.g. card). This covers credit/debit cards and can include other identification devices such as keychain fobs and in time will include virtual inventory such as electronic signatures and keys. An aspect of the administration includes maintaining device reference details and states such as operating system release and age/duration in use.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Administer the issuance of tokens such as cards, fobs etc. to customers. Includes tracking device operating system version tracking and refresh&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Карта аннулируется, а заменяющая карта генерируется и выдается клиенту, сообщившему о краже карты&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот сервисный домен управляет управлением запасами и распределением/выдачей для всех выпущенных устройств и материалов (например, карты). Это распространяется на кредитные / дебетовые карты и может включать в себя другие идентификационные устройства, такие как брелок для ключей и со временем будет включать в себя виртуальный инвентарь, такие как электронные подписи и ключи. Один из аспектов администрирования включает ведение справочных сведений об устройстве и таких состояний, как выпуск операционной системы и возраст/продолжительность использования.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Управление выдачей токенов: таких как карты, брелоки и т. д. для клиентов. Включает отслеживать версию операционной системы прибора отслеживая и освежает&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Issued Device Administration&#xA;This service domain administers the inventory management and allocation/issuance for all issued devices and materials (e.g. cards). This covers credit/debit cards and can include other identification/authentication devices such as keychain fobs. it also handles virtual token inventory such as passwords, secret questions and biometric records (signatures, voice/image). An aspect of the administration includes maintaining device reference details and states such as operating system release and age/duration in use. Specific product/service access permissions can be associated with an issued device&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain administers the issuance of authentication tokens to customers and third party service providers. Tokens here include physical devices such as cards, fobs, readers and intangible 'devices' such as passwords and secret questions. Administration includes version tracking, replacement and duration/frequency limits. Specific product/service access permissions may be associated with an issued token when appropriate&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;Administers the issuance of authentication tokens to customers and third party service providers. Tokens here include physical devices and intangible 'devices' such as passwords and secret questions. Administration includes version tracking, replacement and duration/frequency limits&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A card is cancelled and a replacement card is generated and issued for a customer reporting a stolen card"/>
