<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Sales Product Agreement"
    id="db887c83-ae88-471e-bcd2-b369c6d3b3bc"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;An established customer completes the application process for a new product and a new sales product agreement is established&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;The Sales Product Agreement captures the legal terms of conditions in force for a sold product. This can include many details that influence product and service fulfillment such as applicable fees/rates and selected features/options. It does not however represent the full operating definition/configuration for the products/service as there can be features that are not contractually binding - these features are maintained in the associated product/service fulfillment service domain&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Maintain a structured legal agreement defining the contractual terms and conditions an in-force product.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Установленный клиент завершает процесс подачи заявки на новый продукт и устанавливается новый договор продажи продукта&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Соглашение о продаже продукта отражает юридические условия, действующие для проданного продукта. Это может включать в себя множество деталей, которые влияют на выполнение продукта и услуги, такие как применимые сборы/ставки и выбранные функции/опции. Это, однако, не представляет полное рабочее определение / конфигурацию для продуктов / услуги, поскольку могут быть функции, которые не являются договорно обязательными - эти функции поддерживаются в связанном домене обслуживания выполнения продукта / услуги&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Поддерживать структурированное юридическое соглашение, определяющее условия договора и действующий продукт.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Sales Product Agreement&#xA;The Sales Product Agreement service domain captures and maintains the legal terms and conditions in force for a sold product. The product specific terms and conditions are subordinate to the terms of the customer master agreement that is maintained by the Customer Agreement service domain. The product contractual terms and conditions influence product and service fulfillment for example by defining applicable fees/rates/penalties and selected features/options. Note that there can be other product configuration features that are not contractually binding - these features are maintained in the associated product/service fulfillment service domain directly.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains a structured legal agreement defining the contractual terms and conditions for an in-force product for a customer. It is subordinate to the customer's master agreement that is maintained by the Customer Agreement service domain.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains a structured legal agreement defining the contractual terms and conditions for an in-force product for a customer. It is subordinate to the customer's master agreement that is maintained by the Customer Agreement service domain.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;An established customer completes the application process for a new lending product and a new sales product agreement is established.&#xA;"/>
