<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Advanced Voice Services Operations"
    id="75c6954f-79da-45c6-ab5b-b855a9e203c5"
    documentation="&#xA;Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;The numeric menu is adjusted to increase self serve activity during a period of peak loading (this could be implemented in the IVR in a more sophisticated set-up&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This is the operating schedule for the PBX/telephony infrastructure which can include embedded IVR capabilities. The PBX system will have close integration with the call center and E-Branch capabilities depending on the degree of computer telephony integration (CTI) and cross channel support&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Operate the telephone channel infrastructure, including the IVR and any other automated devices as appropriate. This includes default routing rules and intra-day/session adjustments to deal with peak load or other operational variations&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Числовое меню корректируется, чтобы увеличить обслуживать активности в период пиковой нагрузки (это может быть реализовано в IVR в более сложные настройки&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Это-график работы для инфраструктуры PBX / телефонии, которая может включать встроенные возможности IVR. Система АТС будет иметь тесную интеграцию с возможностями колл-центра и электронного филиала в зависимости от степени интеграции компьютерной телефонии (CTI) и поддержки кросс-каналов&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: При необходимости используйте инфраструктуру телефонных каналов, включая IVR и любые другие автоматизированные устройства. Это включает правила маршрутизации по умолчанию и внутридневные / сеансовые корректировки для работы с пиковой нагрузкой или другими операционными изменениями&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Операции расширенного голосового обслуживания &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Пример:&#xD;&#xA;Настройка голосового меню для увеличения числа случаев самообслуживания клиентов в максимальные часы нагрузки (реализовывается настройками IVR - Interactive Voice Response)&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Описание:&#xD;&#xA;Учет инфраструктуры АТС/телефонии, включая встроенные возможности IVR. &#xD;&#xA;Система УАТС будет тесно интегрирована с колл-центром и возможностями E-Branch (онлайн-каналов) в зависимости от степени интеграции компьютерной телефонии (CTI -  Computer Telephony Integration) и поддержки связанного канала.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Advanced Voice Services Operations&#xA;This service domain handles the operation of the PBX/telephony infrastructure which can include embedded IVR capabilities. The PBX system will have close integration with the call center and E-Branch capabilities depending on the degree of computer telephony integration (CTI) and cross channel support&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain operates the telephone channel infrastructure, including the IVR and any other automated devices as appropriate. This includes handling default routing rules and intra-day/session adjustments to deal with peak load or other operational variations&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain operates the telephone channel infrastructure, including the IVR and any other automated devices as appropriate. This includes handling default routing rules and intra-day/session adjustments to deal with peak load or other operational variations&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;The numeric menu is adjusted to increase self-serve activity during a period of peak loading (this could be implemented in the IVR in a more sophisticated set-up)"/>
