<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Surveys"
    id="569e72ff-9703-43b0-b7a4-ba782f2d5e37"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Business development management determine the number, scope and volume of customer surveys to develop and run. After a new product launch a series of customer surveys are undertaken to assess the take-up and level of customer satisfaction with the new product. The analysis is fed back to the associated business development activities&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain handles the development, deployment and analysis of customer surveys to determine satisfaction levels and highlight areas for procedural and product improvements and/or business and product development opportunities. It is anticipated that the profile, targeting and general planning and assessment of customer surveys is handled within the general business development function rather than by its own dedicated planning service domain as might be necessary in a larger enterprise. Customer surveys might be organized and an integral aspect of campaigns, product design and development and for more general product and service sales, servicing and fulfillment quality assurance efforts.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Define and execute and analyze customer surveys&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Управление развитием бизнеса определите количество, объем и объем опросов клиентов для разработки и запуска. После запуска нового продукта проводится ряд опросов клиентов для оценки поглощения и уровня удовлетворенности клиентов новым продуктом. Анализ возвращается к связанным действиям по развитию бизнеса&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Эта область услуг занимается разработкой, развертыванием и анализом опросов клиентов для определения уровней удовлетворенности и выделения областей для процедурных и продуктовых улучшений и / или возможностей для бизнеса и разработки продуктов. Предполагается, что профиль, адресность и общее планирование и оценка обследований клиентов будут осуществляться в рамках общей функции развития бизнеса, а не в рамках ее собственной выделенной области услуг планирования, которая может потребоваться на более крупном предприятии. Опросы клиентов могут быть организованы и неотъемлемым аспектом кампаний, проектирования и разработки продуктов и для более общих продаж продуктов и услуг, обслуживания и усилий по обеспечению качества выполнения.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Определение, выполнение и анализ опросов клиентов&#xA;"/>
