<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Currency Exchange "
    id="3934c676-337f-43a2-86ea-42038fa8894f"
    documentation="Example of use: &#xA;An over the counter customer exchanges foreign for domestic currency. As the individual is not an established customer, ID details are captured for regulatory purposes and the exchange completed at the prevailing consumer OTC exchange rate plus fees&#xA;&#xA;General Comment:&#xA;This service domain supports physical foreign exchange, typically at a branch or specialist location (some facilities can be supported through the ATM channel). The available domestic and foreign cash inventory is tracked by the Branch Currency Management service domain. As these are typically over the counter (OTC) transactions, there can be bank and regulatory requirements to capture identity details for some transactions. Note that travelers checks and some bank drafts can be considered as a hybrid currency and processed using this same capability though the model has a separate service domain to handle these item&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  This is an over the counter service where currency is exchanged and the transaction uses preferential rates and can include transaction fees. Note in some cases travelers checks can be handled as a pseudo currency within this capability. Note that Branch and teller currency inventory is administered by Branch Currency Management and Branch Currency Distribution service domains&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования: &#xA;Внебиржевой клиент обменивает иностранную валюту на отечественную. Как частное лицо не является клиентом, паспортные данные фиксируются для целей регулирования и биржа завершила сложившимися потребительскими внебиржевой курс плюс сборы&#xA;&#xA;общее замечание:&#xA;Этот сервисный домен поддерживает физический обмен иностранной валюты, как правило, в филиале или специализированном местоположении (некоторые средства могут поддерживаться через канал ATM). Доступный внутренний и внешний наличный запас отслеживается доменом службы Управления валютой филиала. Как правило, это внебиржевые транзакции (OTC), поэтому для некоторых транзакций могут существовать банковские и нормативные требования для получения идентификационных данных. Обратите внимание, что дорожные чеки и некоторые банковские чеки можно рассматривать как гибридную валюту и обрабатывать с помощью этой же возможности, хотя модель имеет отдельный домен обслуживания для обработки этих элементов&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Это внебиржевой сервис, в котором производится обмен валюты, и транзакция использует льготные тарифы и может включать операционные сборы. Примечание в некоторых случаях дорожные чеки могут быть обработаны как псевдо валюты в эту возможность. Обратите внимание, что инвентаризация валюты филиала и кассира управляется доменами службы Управления валютой филиала и распределения валюты филиала&#xA;"/>
