<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Merchant Relations / Торговые отношения"
    id="1b83ee48-8c92-4542-99b7-afa155dd53d3"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A card charge is disputed and a case raised - the case processing requests documentation from the merchant and the resolution is aligned to the payoff ranges governing the agreement&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This candidate service domain is a place holder for a potentially complex array of service domain capabilities needed to manage interbank, merchant relationships and financial capture networks needed to fully support a card product. This is a specialized activity typically outsourced by most banks and so is currently modeled as a 'gateway' relationship rather than a complete range of service domains. In addition to the merchant agreement that determines the transactional fees/terms and rules for dispute resolution, the merchant relationship needs to handle their side of disputes, operation of the merchant network and distributed facilities and some aspects of card inventory management. Note: the internal working of the merchant and financial capture network is not covered in the current release of the BIAN model&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Administer the day to day interactions with merchants, in particular for coordination of case resolution&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Плата за Карту оспаривается и дело поднято-дело обработки запросов документации от продавца и резолюции приведены в соответствие с диапазонами выплат, регулирующих соглашение&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен-кандидат является держателем места для потенциально сложного набора возможностей домена обслуживания, необходимых для управления межбанковскими, торговыми отношениями и сетями финансового захвата, необходимыми для полной поддержки карточного продукта. Это специализированная деятельность, как правило, аутсорсинг большинством банков и поэтому в настоящее время моделируется как отношения &quot;шлюз&quot;, а не полный спектр услуг доменов. В дополнение к торговому соглашению, которое определяет транзакционные сборы / условия и правила разрешения споров, торговые отношения должны обрабатывать свою сторону споров, работу торговой сети и распределенных объектов и некоторые аспекты управления запасами карт. Примечание: внутренняя работа торговой и финансовой сети захвата не покрыта в текущем выпуске модели BIAN&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Администрирование ежедневных взаимодействий с продавцами, в частности, для координации разрешения дел&#xA;"/>
