<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Servicing Activity Analysis"
    id="0645286f-0231-4c60-a170-b2d8d3e2cf1d"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Contact center activity and voice data is analyzed to determine activity profile and performance variation across the contact center workforce. High overhead product/service activities are highlighted&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This handles the analysis of all customer contact activity (typically in the call/contact center but also potentially teller and other customer facing activity, which can include interactive web/device dialogues) to determine the root cause of major issues and/or patterns of activity that can be streamlined or improved&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Analyze consumer servicing position activity, including teller, case/contact center traffic and potentially VoIP activity in more advanced situations. Analysis includes captured call/channel/device type, activity, onward routing and resolution decisions for operational and procedural insights and facility/process and training improvement (Root Cause Analysis)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Деятельность контакт-центра и голосовые данные анализируются для определения профиля деятельности и изменения производительности среди сотрудников контакт-центра. Выделены высокие накладные расходы на продукцию / услуги&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Это обрабатывает анализ всей деятельности контакта с клиентами (как правило, в колл / контакт-центр, но и потенциально кассира и другой деятельности клиента сталкивается, которые могут включать в себя интерактивные диалоги веб / устройства), чтобы определить первопричину основных проблем и / или моделей деятельности, которые могут быть оптимизированы или улучшены&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Анализ активности позиций обслуживания потребителей, включая кассира, трафик case / contact center и потенциально VoIP-активность в более сложных ситуациях. Анализ включает в себя захваченный вызов/канал / тип устройства, деятельность, дальнейшие решения маршрутизации и разрешения для оперативного и процедурного понимания и улучшения объекта / процесса и обучения (анализ первопричин)"/>
