<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Tax Handling"
    id="be8092ad-1b97-4b8b-a704-2881bd24cb99"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A consumer customer is provided with a year end tax report for products and services provided by the bank&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;There are different tax tracking and reporting obligations for products and services in different locations and jurisdictions. This service domain handles the consolidation and reporting of tax related activity as necessary for a customer. Note that additional service domains may be required to handle situations where the bank is responsible for processing tax commitments&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Handle the consumer tax reporting obligations&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Потребительскому клиенту предоставляется налоговый отчет по продуктам и услугам банка на конец года&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Существуют различные обязательства по налоговому отслеживанию и отчетности для продуктов и услуг в разных местах и юрисдикциях. Этот домен услуг обрабатывает консолидацию и отчетность о деятельности, связанной с налогами, по мере необходимости для клиента. Обратите внимание, что для обработки ситуаций, когда банк несет ответственность за обработку налоговых обязательств, могут потребоваться дополнительные Домены обслуживания&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Обрабатывать обязательства по налоговой отчетности потребителей&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Customer Tax Handling&#xA;There are different tax tracking and reporting obligations for products and services in different locations and jurisdictions. This service domain handles the consolidation and reporting of tax related activity as necessary for a customer. Note that this service domain is only responsible for the consolidation and reporting of tax related activity - other service domains will be required to handle actual tax processing obligations as may apply for certain products and services&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain handles consumer tax reporting obligations including the consolidation and reporting of customer tax related financial activity&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A consumer customer is provided with a year end tax report for products and services provided by the bank&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
