<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Prospect Campaign Execution"
    id="b2d61e73-d0f3-4ccf-9c9c-3998bff064ac"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A newly refined prospect campaign (version) is authorized for execution. An operational plan detailing resource allocation, inventory development and task execution is assembled and implemented. The take-up is tracked through the offer management and subsequent product fulfillment processes&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;Prospect campaign execution covers on-going and ad-hoc execution of campaigns, and tracks the impact of implemented campaign versions where a version refers to the deployed instance of the campaign that is tracked for its business impact (this allows for campaign revisions etc.). In addition to handling all of the resource/inventory and task management associated with the deployment of the campaign, the Service Domain also tracks and reports on campaign impact by obtaining intelligence from sales/offer and product fulfillment activities&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Execute a prospect campaign (version) and track and respond to impact&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Недавно уточненная  кампания  для _предполагаемых клиентов_(версия) авторизована для выполнения. Собран и реализован оперативный план, детализирующий распределение ресурсов, разработку запасов и выполнение задач. Поглощение отслеживается через Управление предложением и последующими процессами выполнения продукта&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Перспектива выполнения кампания охватывает и специального исполнения кампаний, и отслеживает воздействие реализована версии там походу версия ссылается на экземпляре кампании, отслеживать ее влияние на бизнес (это позволяет для изменения кампании и т. д.). В дополнение к обработке всех ресурсов/запасов и управлению задачами, связанными с развертыванием кампании, домен службы также отслеживает и сообщает о влиянии кампании, получая сведения о продажах / предложениях и действиях по выполнению продуктов&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Выполнение кампании (версии), отслеживание и реагирование на воздействие.&#xA;"/>
