<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Rewards Points Awards &amp; Redemption"
    id="ada5d116-be66-44d2-a815-12615e2844eb"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A customer redeems reward points to reduce the fees due on another service&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain handles all operational aspects of rewards points fulfillment. The contractual agreement is assumed to be maintained under the master customer agreement that is accessed from here as necessary. Points are allocated to the associated product and service fulfillment activities, here points are redeemed against offered products and services. In a simple implementation rewards points are applied to internal products and services. In a more sophisticated implementation they can be redeemed across multiple merchant facilities and can be transferable into other rewards points programs. Additional service domains may be required to cover more sophisticated rewards points processing&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Handle the allocation and redemption of rewards points for customer transaction activity&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент использует бонусные баллы, чтобы уменьшить сборы за другую услугу&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен услуг обрабатывает все операционные аспекты выполнения бонусных баллов. Предполагается, что договорное соглашение поддерживается в соответствии с Генеральным соглашением с заказчиком, доступ к которому осуществляется отсюда по мере необходимости. Баллы начисляются за соответствующие действия по выполнению продуктов и услуг, здесь баллы списываются с предлагаемых продуктов и услуг. В простой реализации бонусные баллы применяются к внутренним продуктам и услугам. В более сложной реализации они могут быть погашены через несколько торговых объектов и могут быть переданы в другие бонусные баллы программы. Для более сложной обработки бонусных баллов могут потребоваться дополнительные Домены обслуживания&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Обработка распределения и погашения бонусных баллов за операции с клиентами&#xA;"/>
