<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Correspondent Bank"
    id="340fcb16-0f61-4a98-9980-3307680d4fe8"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;Transfer funds from a customer account with the bank to an account with another bank.&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;Correspondent Bank owns the vostro and/or mirror nostro account, with the position delegated to Position Keeping, handles nostro reconciliation, handles incoming and outgoing clearing messages, with the actual sending and receiving delegated to Financial Message Gateway, and handles the settlements.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Fulfils a correspondent bank agreement between the bank and another bank, automated clearing house, etc. Handles the clearing and settlement of payments to/from the correspondent.&#xA;&#xA;Documentation&#xA; Handle payment transactions through the correspondent relationships (with SWIFT) and some other correspondent bank related interactions&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Перевод денежных средств со счета клиента в банке на счет в другом банке.&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Корреспондентский банк владеет счетом vostro и / или mirror nostro, с позицией, делегированной на ведение позиции, обрабатывает сверку nostro, обрабатывает входящие и исходящие клиринговые сообщения, с фактической отправкой и получением, делегированными шлюзу финансовых сообщений, и обрабатывает расчеты.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Выполняет банк-корреспондент договора между банком и другим банком, автоматизированной клиринговой палаты и др. Осуществляет клиринг и расчет платежей корреспонденту/от корреспондента.&#xA;&#xA;Документация&#xA; Обработка платежных операций через корреспондентские отношения (со SWIFT) и некоторые другие взаимодействия, связанные с банком-корреспондентом&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Correspondent Bank&#xA;This Service Domain handles incoming and outgoing payment clearing and settlement messages to the bank's correspondent banking partners. The actual message transmission is delegated to the Financial Message Gateway service domain. Correspondent Bank administers the mirror accounting for interbank payments undertaking the underlying account reconciliation tasks.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain fulfils correspondent banking arrangements between the bank and its correspondent banking partners.  This includes handling the clearing and settlement of payments to/from the correspondent banks, typically using the SWIFT payment network.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain fulfills correspondent banking arrangements between the bank and its correspondent banking partners. This includes handling the clearing and settlement of payments to/from the correspondent banks, typically using the SWIFT payment network.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;Transfer funds from a customer account with the bank to an account with another bank.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
