<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Fraud Detection"
    id="047cc61f-6b9e-498e-ac17-e676ef2d34f0"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;A collection of accounting records and financial transactions is subjected to an array of fraud scanners to detect possible patterns of fraudulent behavior&#xA;++++A fraudulent use of a stolen card is detected and passed for resolution&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;This service center handles the structured execution of fraud detection/scanner routines. In practice many scanners run within different production facilities and possible anomalies are reported for further analysis by this service domain. Detected instances of possible fraud are escalated for resolution&#xA;++++This service domain handles the structured execution of fraud detection tests/routines that are used to identify possible fraud. The tests may run in-line with production or may access transaction logs as appropriate. Detected anomalies are passed for further analysis and resolution&#xA;++++The Fraud Case service domain handles the full analysis of a detected fraud case and orchestrates all resolution actions. This can include making suggestions for changes to production arrangements to reduce exposure to future repeated fraud attempts&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Execute fraud behavior pattern scanners and threshold based transaction triggering of possible fraudulent/AML activity&#xA;++++The service domains executes fraud behavioral pattern tests to detect possible fraudulent transactions/activity&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Коллекция учетных записей и финансовых операций подвергается множеству сканеров мошенничества для обнаружения возможных моделей мошеннического поведения&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Этот сервисный центр осуществляет структурированное выполнение процедур обнаружения мошенничества / сканирования. На практике многие сканеры работают на различных производственных объектах, и в этой области услуг сообщается о возможных аномалиях для дальнейшего анализа. Выявлены случаи возможного мошенничества, передаются для разрешения&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Выполнение сканеров шаблонов мошеннического поведения и пороговых транзакций, запускающих возможные мошеннические действия&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Fraud Detection&#xA;This service domain handles the structured execution of fraud detection tests/routines that are used to identify possible fraud. The tests may run in-line with production or may access transaction logs as appropriate. Detected anomalies are passed for further analysis and resolution&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;&#xA;The service domains executes fraud behavioral pattern tests to detect possible fraudulent transactions/activity"/>
