<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Credit Management"
    id="e5d50e90-3770-461a-85bb-a3e12c2ad604"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A corporate loan is presented for credit management pricing decisioning prior to completion of the offer process&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain supports a central bank credit management function that supports a credit perspective across all bank activity. Transactions can be repriced to factor in the credit perspective&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  A bank-wide function to qualify credit pricing for offered products and services to reflect the bank's appetite to write the business (overrides the standard product pricing procedure)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Корпоративный кредит предоставляется для принятия решения о ценообразовании кредитного менеджмента до завершения процесса предложения&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен услуг поддерживает функцию управления кредитами Центрального банка, которая поддерживает кредитную перспективу во всей банковской деятельности. Сделки могут быть переоценены с учетом кредитной перспективы&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Общебанковская функция для квалификации кредитного ценообразования для предлагаемых продуктов и услуг, чтобы отразить аппетит банка, чтобы написать бизнес (переопределяет стандартную процедуру ценообразования продукта)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Credit Management&#xA;This service domain supports a central bank credit management function that maintains an overarching credit perspective across all bank activity. Transactions can be re-priced to factor in this credit perspective.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain provides a bank-wide/oversight function to qualify credit pricing for offered products and services to reflect the bank's appetite to write the business. This decision can override the standard product pricing procedure.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain provides a bank-wide/oversight function to qualify credit pricing for offered products and services to reflect the bank's appetite to write the business. This decision can override the standard product pricing procedure&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A corporate loan is presented for credit management pricing decisioning prior to completion of the offer process&#xA;&#xA;"/>
