<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Position Keeping"
    id="324110ee-9391-464c-b217-aa7ea115bd55"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;Any product fulfillment domain, current account, savings account, credit card, etc, has a position with Position Keeping. A multi-currency account has multiple positions, one for each currency.&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;Position Keeping is the proverbial sock that holds money. It keeps a record of all debit and credit entries to the position, computing the various balances of the position. It's up to the owner, the service domain that created the position, to understand the context of the position. Authorisation of the entry is delegated to/handled by the owning service domain. Position Keeping manages the changes to the balance, but the actual computation of interest is left to the owner of the position.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Administer the debit and credit entries against a financial position, keeping track of the balance.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Любой домен выполненный продукт, текущие счета, сберегательные счета, кредитные карты и т. д., имеет место с отслеживанием_статуса. Мультивалютный счет имеет несколько _статусов, по одной для каждой валюты.&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Отслеживание_статуса пресловутый носок который держит деньги. Он ведет учет всех статсуов_ дебетовых и кредитных операций , вычисляя различные балансы позиции. Это зависит от владельца, домена службы, который создал _статус_, чтобы понять контекст _статуса_. Авторизация записи делегируется/ обрабатывается доменом-владельцем службы. Отслеживание_статуса управляет изменениями баланса, но фактический расчет процентов остается за владельцем статуса.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Администрирование дебетовых и кредитных операций по финансовому статусу_, отслеживание баланса.&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Position Keeping&#xA;Position Keeping is the service domain that maintains transaction journals for a wide range of bank activities - product fulfillment in particular.  It keeps a record of all debit and credit entries to the position. It can offer utilities that enable it to maintain balances/positions, to calculate interest and to support account reconciliation activities. Position keeping may support accounts in multiple currencies and conforming to different accounting rules as needed&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain administers the debit and credit entries made against a financial account/position, keeping track of the balance (a transaction journal)&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain administers the debit and credit entries made against a financial account/position, keeping track of the balance (a transaction journal)&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;Any product fulfillment domain, current account, savings account, credit card, etc, delegates transaction posting/track to the Position Keeping service domain&#xA;"/>
