<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Card Case"
    id="5f481788-b632-40f3-bb4f-2697414fcb94"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A card holder reports a payment dispute to the contact center and a case is initiated. The account is credited and documentation requested from the merchant. The case is finally judged when the documents are available for review and all interested parties are notified of the resolution&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;It is questionable whether a service domain specifically for card cases is required, or whether the general case resolution service domain can cover all types of (consumer) cases. As there are very specific card processing cases, at this stage a card specific service domain is included in the BIAN landscape&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Capture, track, resolve and report on card related transactional disputes (includes card use and payment issues)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Владелец карты сообщает в контакт-центр о споре по оплате и инициирует дело. Счет зачисляется и документация запрашивается у продавца. Дело, наконец, рассудили, когда документы доступны для рассмотрения и все заинтересованные стороны уведомлены о резолюции&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Сомнительно, требуется ли домен службы специально для обращений с картами или домен службы разрешения общих обращений может охватывать все типы обращений (потребителей). Поскольку есть очень определенные случаи обработки карты, на данном этапе карта определенный сервисный домен включена в ландшафт BIAN&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Захват, отслеживание, разрешение и отчет по транзакционным спорам, связанным с картой (включая вопросы использования карты и оплаты)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Card Case&#xA;Capture, track, resolve and report on card related transactional disputes, handling all the dispute resolution messages between the Issuer, the Card Network and the Acquirer.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain handles the processing of a customer card case, typically a disputed charge&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A card holder reports a payment dispute to the contact center and a case is initiated. The account is credited and documentation requested from the merchant. The case is finally judged when the documents are available for review and all interested parties are notified of the resolution&#xA;"/>
