<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Servicing Event History"
    id="bf9ac0b6-28fd-46a3-94af-865497ccfc3f"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A servicing contact is concluded and the contact details and result is captured. In cases the call is recorded&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;The service domain captures the details of servicing activity to support root cause analysis. This can include capturing actual dialogue for training and support facility design&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Capture, classify and store servicing activity and events to support root cause analysis&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Контракт на обслуживание заключен и детали контакта и результат захвачены. В случаях, когда звонок записан&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Домен службы фиксирует сведения об обслуживании для поддержки анализа основных причин. Это может включать в себя захват фактического диалога для обучения и поддержки проектирования объекта&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Захват, классификация и хранение операций и событий обслуживания для поддержки анализа основных причин&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Servicing Event History&#xA;The Servicing Event History service domain captures the details of servicing activity to support root cause analysis. The information captured can include summary details of the servicing activity, product access details and click-stream/voice records as necessary. The captured detail can be analyzed for staff assessment and training and to support procedural refinements&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain captures, classifies and stores servicing activity and events to support root cause analysis&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain captures, classifies and stores servicing activity and events to support root cause analysis&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A servicing contact is concluded and the contact details and result is captured. In cases the call is recorded&#xA;&#xA;"/>
