<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Financial Gateway"
    id="daf3ec75-f3af-431e-9949-c41cff6850f1"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;During the 24 hour cycle, the bank's 'wire room' unit establishes the connections with the different payments, SWIFT and reporting networks&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;This service domain supports the operational connections with the range of financial networks that support interbank and financial institution connectivity. This includes SWIFT, ACH gateways, and market regulatory reporting connections. The service domain does not create content itself, it provides a message exchange service between (financial) institutions. One of its responsibilities is to route a message to the destination specified by the caller, but it does not decide the destination itself.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Operate automated message interfaces to secure networks such as SWIFT, TELEX, ACH and Exchange reporting services&#xA;&#xA;Documentation&#xA; Connects applications to secure network(s) for the exchange of financial messages&#xA;Manages and uses exchange channels internally&#xA;Decides ? where to route the message (externally, internally)&#xA;Decides ? what to batch/straight through – timing&#xA;Does not ? know business cut-off times&#xA;Knows the syntax of the message (incl. content?)&#xA;Does not ? know the semantics of the message content&#xA;Separate SD for gateway vs message manager&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;В течение 24-часового цикла подразделение банка &quot;wire room&quot; устанавливает связь с различными платежными, SWIFT и отчетными сетями&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Эта область услуг поддерживает оперативные связи с целым рядом финансовых сетей, поддерживающих межбанковскую связь и связь с финансовыми учреждениями. Это включает в себя SWIFT, ACH шлюзы и подключения к отчетности по регулированию рынка. Домен сервиса не создает контент сам по себе, он предоставляет услугу обмена сообщениями между (финансовыми) учреждениями. Одна из его обязанностей состоит в том, чтобы направить сообщение в место, указанное звонившим, но не решает саму цель.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Использование автоматизированных интерфейсов сообщений для защиты сетей, таких как SWIFT, TELEX, ACH и Exchange reporting services.&#xA;&#xA;Документация&#xA; Подключение приложений к защищенным сетям для обмена финансовыми сообщениями&#xA;Управление и использование каналов exchange&#xA;Решает ? куда направить сообщение (внешне, внутренне)&#xA;Решает ? что к серии / прямо через-время&#xA;Разве нет ? знайте времена выключения дела&#xA;Знает синтаксис сообщения (ВКЛ. содержание?)&#xA;Разве нет ? знать семантику содержимого сообщения &#xA;Отдельный SD для шлюза и диспетчера сообщений&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Financial Gateway&#xA;This service domain supports the operational connections with the range of financial networks that support interbank and financial institution connectivity. This includes SWIFT, ACH gateways, and market exchange/regulatory reporting connections. The service domain does not create content itself, it provides a message exchange service between (financial) institutions for various units within the bank. It may format messages and maintain and apply authentication and encryption keys to the transmitted messages and necessary. It also provides operational message recovery and re-transmission facilities as appropriate&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain operates automated message interfaces to secure networks such as SWIFT, TELEX, ACH and Financial Market/Exchange reporting services&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;During the 24 hour cycle, the bank's 'wire room' unit establishes the connections with the different payments, SWIFT and reporting networks&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
