<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Regulatory Compliance"
    id="dc4929bf-4590-459a-81cd-57642c2c75ff"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A new customer's details are passed for regulatory watch list checks. A subsequent transaction is reported for regulatory compliance checks&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain administers the scheduled and ad-hoc application of regulatory checks. This includes determining which regulations apply in specific circumstances and the subsequent application of the associated tests.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Interpret regulatory requirements and define a portfolio of regulatory compliance tests across all appropriate activities. Relate the regulatory checks to activities as necessary&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Данные нового клиента передаются для проверки по контрольному списку. Последующая транзакция сообщается для проверки соответствия нормативным требованиям&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен служб управляет запланированным и нерегламентированным применением регуляторных проверок. Это включает определение того, какие правила применяются в конкретных обстоятельствах, и последующее применение соответствующих испытаний.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Интерпретация нормативных требований и определение портфеля тестов на соответствие нормативным требованиям по всем соответствующим видам деятельности. Соотнесите регулирующие проверки с деятельностью по мере необходимости&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Regulatory Compliance&#xA;This service domain administers the scheduled and ad-hoc application of regulatory checks. This includes interpreting the full range of regulatory requirements governing the bank's operations and determining which regulations apply in specific circumstances across the enterprise. Support and guidelines are provided to activities in the bank that are subject to the regulations and scheduled and ad-hoc checks performed to confirm compliance&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain provides a service to interpret regulatory requirements, provide guidance and define and implement a portfolio of regulatory compliance tests across all appropriate bank activities&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A new customer's details are passed for regulatory watch list checks. A subsequent transaction is reported for regulatory compliance checks&#xA;"/>
