<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Financial Market Research"
    id="0de7e666-81d5-4e8b-bad7-fdb4d9d87293"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Financial Market Analysis requests consolidated and scrubbed market intelligence referring to a specific corporation&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain covers the access and consolidation of a potentially wide range of market research topics and sources. The consolidated intelligence will typically target one or more companies, products or market segments that can inform trading activity. The capability can include activities that qualify, classify and scrub imported intelligence and organize it for more effective selection/retrieval for review and analysis. Some organizations may include sophisticated and complex market intelligence gathering activities for which additional Service Domains may be required to fully model this activity&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Consolidate financial market information from a variety of sources and optionally organize the consolidated information to align to different topics or categories for subsequent selection and analysis (see Financial Market Analysis)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Запросы на анализ финансового рынка консолидированная и очищенная рыночная аналитика, относящаяся к конкретной корпорации&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Эта область услуг охватывает доступ и консолидацию потенциально широкого круга тем и источников маркетинговых исследований. Консолидированная аналитика, как правило, нацелена на одну или несколько компаний, продуктов или сегментов рынка, которые могут информировать торговую деятельность. Эта возможность может включать мероприятия, которые квалифицируют, классифицируют и очищают импортированную разведывательную информацию и организуют ее для более эффективного отбора/извлечения для обзора и анализа. Некоторые организации могут включать сложные и сложные мероприятия по сбору рыночной информации, для которых могут потребоваться дополнительные Домены услуг для полного моделирования этой деятельности&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Консолидация информации о финансовом рынке из различных источников и дополнительная организация консолидированной информации для согласования с различными темами или категориями для последующего выбора и анализа (см. Анализ финансового рынка)&#xA;"/>
