<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Party Authentication"
    id="eb8579e2-2009-4d0e-b543-ad2c396e9c98"
    documentation=" : Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A customer is authenticated making contact through a channel&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;Currently authentication is a cross channel capability that may use any device/tag or secret information to authenticate a party. Channel or device specific variations may be required. It is assumed a number of authentication levels will be defined for a deployment&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  A cross channel capability that provides contact verification for a customer accessing the bank&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;: Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент аутентифицируется, устанавливая контакт через канал&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;В настоящее время аутентификация является кросс-канальной возможностью, которая может использовать любое устройство / метку или секретную информацию для аутентификации стороны. Изменения канала или прибора специфические могут необходимы. Предполагается, что для развертывания будет определено несколько уровней проверки подлинности&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;Возможность кросс-канала, который обеспечивает проверку контакта для клиента, обращающегося в банк&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Party Authentication&#xA;Customer authentication is a cross-channel/device capability that provides identity confirmation for customers accessing the bank through any interactive channel. The service may use a combination of one or more mechanisms to authenticate including issued tokens/devices, virtual mechanisms such as passwords and bio-metrics such as voice/face recognition. Different levels of authentication may be determined to support different types of access and there may be access permissions associated with the authentication mechanism used.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain provides a customer identify authentication service covering all channels and devices to support access to the banks products and services.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain provides a customer identify authentication service covering all channels and devices to support access to the banks products and services.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A customer is authenticated when making phone contact with the bank's service center.&#xA;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;"/>
