<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Card Authorization"
    id="7885c4e8-aaef-4a09-8104-f527820169cb"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A credit card customer makes a large purchase, the card authorization triggers a verbal check of the customer details for security and the authorization is given&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain is responsible for the real time card authorization decisions for credit/charge cards. The authorization decision is automated and can be extremely complex. Transactions may be passed for manual checks by on-line service representatives for out of pattern purchases. Note that authorized transaction amounts may vary from the actual final amount (e.g. pre authorized hotel/car hire and charged meals excluding tips) and in cases there will be no financial transaction for an authorized transaction if the customer chooses to pay using a different card/cash&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Execute the decision based authorization and recording of proposed card transactions through the merchant network&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент кредитной карты совершает крупную покупку, авторизация карты запускает устную проверку данных клиента на безопасность и авторизация дается&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот сервисный домен отвечает за принятие решений об авторизации кредитной/платежной карты в режиме реального времени. Решение об авторизации автоматизировано и может быть чрезвычайно сложным. Сделки могут быть переданы для ручной проверки представителями онлайн-сервиса для внеплановых покупок. Обратите внимание, что сумма авторизованной транзакции может отличаться от фактической окончательной суммы (например, предварительно авторизованный отель / прокат автомобилей и оплаченное питание, за исключением чаевых) , и в случаях, когда для санкционированной транзакции не будет финансовой транзакции, если клиент решит оплатить с помощью другой карты / наличными&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Выполнить авторизацию на основе решения и регистрацию предлагаемых операций по карте через торговую сеть&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Card Authorization&#xA;The proposed card transaction is requested by a merchant and routed through the Acquirer and Card Network to the Issuer. The authorization decision is automated and can be extremely complex. Transactions may be passed for manual checks by on-line service representatives for out of pattern purchases. Note that authorized transaction amounts may vary from the actual final amount (e.g. pre authorized hotel/car hire and charged meals excluding tips) and in cases there will be no financial transaction for an authorized transaction if the customer chooses to pay using a different card/cash. While this function is primarily performed by the Issuer, Acquirers and Card Networks may perform Stand-in Authorization and forward the results to the Issuer for recording.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain is responsible for the real time card authorization decisions for credit/charge cards.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A credit card customer makes a large purchase, the card authorization triggers a verbal check of the customer details for security and the authorization is given&#xA;"/>
