<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Fraud/AML Resolution"
    id="af32a2b6-e662-4c06-b466-30c1d8d8aab6"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A pattern of possible fraud is highlighted in transaction records that is researched and evidence of fraud discovered. Prosecution is initiated&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain handles the resolution of detected fraud and AML issues in production. Typically a specialist team that handles each case as a project with a structured procedure for analysis and resolution tasks&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Review, diagnose and respond to detected production activity that has been identified as potential fraud/AML behavior&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;В отчетах о сделках, которые изучаются и обнаруживаются доказательства мошенничества, указывается на характер возможного мошенничества. Возбуждено уголовное преследование &#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен обслуживания обрабатывает разрешение обнаруженных проблем мошенничества и AML в производстве. Как правило, команда специалистов, которая обрабатывает каждый случай как проект со структурированной процедурой анализа и решения задач&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Анализ, диагностика и реагирование на обнаруженную производственную деятельность, которая была определена как потенциальное мошенничество&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Fraud AML Resolution&#xA;This service domain handles the diagnosis/confirmation of detected potential fraud and AML issues in production. Typically the service is supported with specialist teams to  handle cases with structured procedures and techniques for analysis and undertaking the required resolution/escalation tasks.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain reviews, diagnoses and responds to potential fraud/AML behavior that has been detected during production processing.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain reviews, diagnoses and responds to potential fraud/AML behavior that has been detected during production processing&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A pattern of possible fraud is highlighted in transaction records that is researched and evidence of fraud discovered. Prosecution/resolution activity is initiated.&#xA;&#xA;"/>
