<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Location Data Management"
    id="380ce907-dc35-495a-ba31-019070b8556c"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Maintain the layout and use of a shopping center that is referenced for on-line marketing&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;The maintenance of location details is used to support more dynamic sales and servicing activities enabled by mobile devices and tracking. At a basic level validity checks are provided, but more interactive uses can also be supported&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Maintain details of the use and state of locations of interest (e.g. shops)&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;ЯндексПереводчик&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Ведение макета и использование торгового центра, на который ссылается интернет-маркетинг&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Обслуживание сведений о местоположении используется для поддержки более динамичных операций продаж и обслуживания с помощью мобильных устройств и отслеживания. На базовом уровне предусмотрены проверки валидности, но могут поддерживаться и более интерактивные применения&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Сохранение сведений об использовании и состоянии интересующих объектов (например, магазинов)&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Location Data Management&#xA;The maintenance of location details is used to check the validity, allowed use and occupancy of locations - both physical and virtual. This information can be augmented using external directory services when appropriate. The information is used for authentication and security purposes, and can also be used for interactive location based sales and marketing when combined with location tracking services/capabilities&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains details of the use and state of locations of interest to the bank. This can include both physical and virtual addresses. It is used to check for valid use and for sales/marketing activities&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A new prospect provides an address as their place of residence. It is checked to be a valid/known location for residential use.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
