<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Guideline Compliance"
    id="f97655f5-3b51-4975-8d7a-a812d8035a3e"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A loan origination process is submitted for guideline compliance checks prior to completing the origination process&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service center administers the activity of a specialists tasked with testing and confirming guideline compliance. This is typically focused on investment and loan activities, confirming transactions are executed in alignment with management guidelines and policies.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Develop and apply a portfolio of guideline compliance tests to confirm adherence to agreed and regulatory imposed internal procedures (note one particular area of focus is investment management). Test on complete transaction data or a meaningful sample as appropriate to mitigate exposure to non-compliant behaviors&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Процесс получения кредита представляется для проверки соответствия руководящим принципам до завершения процесса порождения&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот сервисный центр управляет деятельностью специалистов, которым поручено тестирование и подтверждение соответствия руководящим принципам. Это, как правило, сосредоточены на инвестиционной и кредитной деятельности, подтверждающие сделки выполняются в соответствии с руководящими принципами и политикой.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Разработка и применение портфеля тестов соответствия руководящим принципам для подтверждения соблюдения согласованных и нормативных внутренних процедур (Примечание. одной из конкретных областей является Управление инвестициями). Тестирование полных данных транзакций или значимого образца в зависимости от ситуации для снижения риска несоответствующего поведения&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Guideline Compliance&#xA;This service center administers the activity of a specialists tasked with testing and confirming guideline compliance. Compliance tests may include document reviews, more detailed transaction analysis and may involve interactions with the unit under test to obtain additional detail/explanation. Guideline compliance is typically focused on larger value investment and loan activities, confirming transactions are executed in alignment with management guidelines and prudential policies.&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;&#xA;This service domain develops and applies a portfolio of guideline compliance tests to confirm adherence to bank and regulator imposed internal procedures. Tests may be made on complete transaction data or a meaningful samples as appropriate to mitigate exposure to non-compliant behaviors. Compliance checks may be in response to a schedule, a specific request as part of normal processing or may be initiated randomly as an oversight activity&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain develops and applies a portfolio of guideline compliance tests to confirm adherence to bank and regulator imposed internal procedures. Tests may be made on complete transaction data or a meaningful samples as appropriate to mitigate exposure to non-compliant behaviors.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A loan origination process is submitted for guideline compliance checks prior to completing the origination/loan closure process&#xA;"/>
