<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Card Terminal Administration"
    id="c0fff0fa-d9b8-4818-b892-dbaff24d268b"
    documentation="&#xA;&#xA;Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A Merchant is assigned one or more devices or interfaces for processing Card Charge authorization and submission when an Acquiring Bank sets up a new Merchant Account. This may be a Point of Sale Terminal or an Authorization Link interface to the merchant's own cash register system. The Acquiring Bank configures the terminal or the interface to meet the specific requirements of the Merchant depending on the merchant type, risk and other terms and conditions.&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain is responsible for the allocation of the Point of Sale Terminal of Authorization Link interface to the Merchant, configuring and activating the device or interface, and managing its ongoing status, including replacement of faulty devices or interfaces.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Administer the POS Network including the inventory, terminal characteristics, deployment and status of the POS devices.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Продавцу назначается одно или несколько устройств или интерфейсов для обработки авторизации и отправки платежей по карте, когда банк-эквайер создает новый торговый счет. Это может быть терминал точки продажи или интерфейс авторизационной ссылки на собственную кассовую систему продавца. Банк-эквайер настраивает терминал или интерфейс под конкретные требования Мерчанта в зависимости от типа мерчанта, риска и других условий.&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Данный сервисный домен отвечает за выделение продавцу терминала точки продажи интерфейса Authorization Link, настройку и активацию устройства или интерфейса, а также за управление его текущим состоянием, включая замену неисправных устройств или интерфейсов.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Администрирование сети POS, включая инвентаризацию, характеристики терминалов, развертывание и состояние устройств POS.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Card Terminal Administration&#xA;This service domain is responsible for the allocation of the Point of Sale Terminal of Authorization Link interface to the Merchant, configuring and activating the device or interface, and managing its ongoing status, including replacement of faulty devices or interfaces. The Acquiring Bank configures the terminal or the interface to meet the specific requirements of the Merchant depending on the merchant type, risk and other terms and conditions.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain administers the POS Network including the inventory, terminal characteristics, deployment and status of the POS devices.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A Merchant is assigned one or more devices or interfaces for processing Card Charge authorization and submission when an Acquiring Bank sets up a new Merchant Account. (Note this can involve a Point of Sale Terminal or an Authorization Link interface to the merchant's own cash register system)&#xA;&#xA;"/>
