<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Card eCommerce Gateway"
    id="a5cd1464-b3a4-4c74-bbb8-84c6e79fe91f"
    documentation="&#xA;&#xA;Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;When a Card is used for making a payment on an e-commerce site of a Merchant, the Merchant initiates three steps to process the payment: 1) request authentication of the Card and the Cardholder, 2) request an authorization of the charge amount, and 3) submit the charge details to the Card Acquirer for processing and payment.&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain is used by the Card Acquiring bank to handle the authentication, authorization and submission of a Card payment from an e-commerce merchant. It supports the 3-D Secure method of authentication which routes the authentication request to the Card Issuing Bank, which may use multi-factor authentication for the authentication of the Card and the Cardholder. It also handles the routing of the authorization request through the Card Transaction Switch service domain and the routing of the submitted charges to the Card Clearing service domain.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Orchestrate the processing of e-commerce transactions for authentication, authorization and capture of the financial transactions.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Когда карта используется для совершения платежа на e-коммерция веб-сайт продавца, то продавец инициирует три шага, чтобы процесс оплаты: 1) запрос на проверку подлинности карты и держателя карты, 2) запрос авторизации в общую сумму платежа, и 3) представить обвинение детали на карту приобретателя для обработки и оплаты.&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот сервисный домен используется банком-эквайером карт для аутентификации, авторизации и отправки Карточного платежа от продавца электронной коммерции. Он поддерживает 3-D безопасный метод аутентификации, который направляет запрос Аутентификации в банк-эмитент карты, который может использовать многофакторную аутентификацию для аутентификации карты и владельца карты. Он также обрабатывает маршрутизацию запроса авторизации через домен службы коммутатора транзакций карт и маршрутизацию отправленных платежей в домен службы очистки карт.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Организация обработки транзакций электронной торговли для аутентификации, авторизации и отслеживания финансовых транзакций.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Card ECommerce Gateway&#xA;This service domain is used by the Card Acquiring bank to handle the authentication, authorization and submission of a Card payment from an e-commerce merchant. It supports the &quot;&quot;3-D&quot;&quot; Secure method of authentication which routes the authentication request to the Card Issuing Bank, which may use multi-factor authentication for the authentication of the Card and the Cardholder. It also handles the routing of the authorization request through the Card Transaction Switch service domain and the routing of the submitted charges to the Card Clearing service domain.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain orchestrates the processing of e-commerce transactions for authentication, authorization and capture of the financial transactions.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;When a Card is used to make a payment on an eCommerce site of a Merchant, the Merchant initiates 3 steps to process: Request authentication of the Card and the Cardholder, Request an authorization of the charge amount, Submit the charge details to the Card Acquirer for processing and payment&#xA;"/>
