<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Position"
    id="ecb84762-f6fa-4906-957f-f791028782fc"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;The banks maintains and analysies the consolidated position for a customer across all accounts products and services&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;Position Management maintians the transaction journal for a single product or function and is used for transaction reconciliation and financial booking. This Service Domain pulls together the derived financial position across all products and services and may combine actual and estimated exposures&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Maintain a consolidated financial position of a customer&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;Банки поддерживают и анализируют консолидированный статус клиента по всем продуктам и услугам счетов&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;Управление статусами ведение журнала проводок для одного продукта или функции и используется для выверки проводок и финансового резервирования. Эта область обслуживания объединяет производное финансовый _статус_ по всем продуктам и услугам и может объединять фактические и оценочные риски&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Поддержание консолидированного финансового положения клиента&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Customer Position&#xA;Individual products will maintain different financial views for the customer. This service domain consolidates financial details from all in-force products and services in order to derive a consolidated financial view which can include current (real-time) positions and projected/estimated values. The consolidated customer position can cover aspects such as cash flows/balances, credit and collateral positions and may derive actual and estimated/projected values&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain maintains a consolidated financial position for a customer, combining details from all products and services in use. The position can cover available funds, credit, collateral, tax exposure and other financial measures as necessary&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;The banks maintains and analyses the consolidated position for a customer across all accounts products and services"/>
