<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Payment Order"
    id="37a1f7d9-de5a-45c1-b745-13a751c6e274"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A customer initiates a payment order to transfer funds to an account in another bank &#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;Payment Order handles the customer side of a payment, the movement of money from debtor to creditor. It handles preparing, changing, cancelling, and committing the payment, authorisation of the payment by the customer, verification that the customer has an agreement to issue the payment, and warehousing of future-dated payments. The actual execution of the payment, figuring out how to reach the debtor and creditor account, is delegated to Payment Execution.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Support customers in creating, changing, authorising and tracking execution of payment orders.&#xA;&#xA;Documentation&#xA; Manages the customer side of payments:&#xA;Move money from A to B, never mind the specific location of A and B, now or in future&#xA;Typically invoked from a customer channel SD, or from a product fulfilment SD.&#xA;Invokes SD Customer Agreement to check for authorisation and applicable transaction fees (when included in the Payment Transaction).&#xA;Delegates actual execution of the payment to SD Payment Execution.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент инициирует платежное поручение для перевода средств на счет в другом банке &#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Платежное поручение обрабатывает сторону платежа клиента, движение денег от должника к кредитору. Он обрабатывает подготовку, изменение, отмену и совершение платежа, авторизацию платежа клиентом, проверку того, что у клиента есть соглашение на выпуск платежа, и складирование будущих платежей. Фактическое исполнение платежа, выяснение того, как добраться до счета должника и кредитора, делегируется исполнению платежа.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Поддержка клиентов в создании, изменении, авторизации и отслеживании выполнения платежных поручений.&#xA;&#xA;Документация&#xA; Управляет платежной стороной клиента:&#xA;Переместить деньги из А В б, не говоря уже о конкретном месте А и Б, сейчас или в будущем&#xA;Обычно вызывается из SD канала клиента или из SD выполнения продукта.&#xA;Ссылается на договор с клиентом СД для проверки авторизации и оплаты сделки (когда включены в платеж).&#xA;Делегирует фактическое выполнение платежа исполнению SD-платежа.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;++++&#xA;Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;- A verified credit transfer instruction is taken in, an AML check on the beneficiary is performed and the execution of Payment Execution is initiated.&#xA;&#xA;- Direct Debit has taken in a batch of direct debit instructions from a corporate customer. For each direct debit a Payment Order is initiated.&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;Payment Order can be initated by Payment Initiation (for instance for an outgoing credit transfer) and Direct Debit (to create a Payment Order for one Direct Debit), but also for an internal process from a fulfilment domain (charging an account opening fee)&#xA;&#xA;For outgoing credit transfers, the sequence of invocation is Payment Initiation - Payment Order - Payment Execution.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;+++&#xA;Service Domain - Payment Order&#xA;Payment Order handles the internal bank and compliance checks and processing of funds transfers prior to initiating the actual mechanics of transfer which is handled by the service domain Payment Execution. This includes watch-list and other regulatory checks and applying any counterparty specific limits and payment preferences. It may also oversee payment netting arrangements between the bank and other counterparties&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain handles the bank-side processing of funds transfers, making the necessary bank and regulatory checks on the involved parties and applying their payment preferences where appropriate&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A customer transaction results in the generation of a payment order to transfer funds to an account in another bank&#xA;"/>
