<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Behavior Models"
    id="f56a5fa0-a142-4989-9d89-57f8a8020a7c"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;Decision scientists track the use and impact of behavior models and make design improvements to enhance their accuracy&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain handles the development, maintenance and assessment of the collection of customer behavior models that are deployed across the bank. This includes more general analyses for sales, operational behavior, relationship development and specific behaviors such as credit and fraud detection. Customer can cover consumer, corporate and merchant behavior for some behavioral models/scanners&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Assess the coverage and impact of the portfolio of customer behavior models and develop and refine the portfolio of available models&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Специалисты по принятию решений отслеживают использование и влияние моделей поведения и улучшают дизайн для повышения их точности&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен обслуживания отвечает за разработку, обслуживание и оценку коллекции моделей поведения клиентов, развернутых в банке. Это включает в себя более общий анализ продаж, операционного поведения, развития отношений и специфического поведения, такого как кредит и выявление мошенничества. Клиент может покрыть потребительское, корпоративное и торговое поведение для некоторых поведенческих моделей / сканеров&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Оценить охват и влияние портфеля моделей поведения клиентов, а также разработать и усовершенствовать портфель доступных моделей&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Customer Behavior Models&#xA;This service domain references the range of customer historical data maintained by the Customer Event History service domain to develop behavioral insights into customers. This analysis can support sales and marketing activity (e.g. by determining the likely response to sales efforts based on passed performance) as well as identifying changes in status and behavior that might influence the desired product mix for a customer. The actual analysis routines are developed/maintained by the Customer Behavior Models service domain&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain applies behavioral analysis to customer event history to maintain a range of customer ratings/scores (such as 'propensity to buy') and to detect life events or trends&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain applies behavioral analysis to customer event history to maintain a range of customer ratings/scores (such as 'propensity to buy') and to detect life events or trends&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A regular analysis of customer event histories is used to update the maintained range of customer behavioral insights. The updated results are notified to the Customer Relationship Management and Party Profile Service Domains as appropriate&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
