<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Customer Workbench"
    id="613d4fa2-b9d0-4863-b878-1f3573f8d0b3"
    documentation="Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A customer downloads an end user financial management application offered by the bank&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain handles the distribution and operation of a client based facility to support local working and access to the banks different products and services. It allows for the customer to maintain information and configuration settings remotely to govern their own access environment as necessary. The service domain is external to the bank, but is included as it may run application capabilities that are either provide by or certified for use by the bank.&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Provide a customer access portal to the banks products and services through any suitable channel and device&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент загружает предлагаемое банком приложение финансового управления для конечного пользователя&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот домен служба осуществляет распределение и эксплуатацию установки клиента на основе поддержки местных рабочих и доступ к банкам разных продуктов и услуг. Это позволяет клиенту поддерживать информацию и параметры конфигурации удаленно управлять своей собственной средой доступа по мере необходимости. Домен службы является внешним по отношению к банку, но включен в него, поскольку в нем могут выполняться возможности приложений, предоставляемые банком или сертифицированные для использования банком.&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;:: Обеспечить портал доступа клиентов к продуктам и услугам банка через любой подходящий канал и устройство&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Customer Workbench&#xA;This service domain handles the distribution and operation of a client device based/resident facility to support local working and access to the banks different products and services. It allows for the customer to maintain information and configuration settings remotely to govern their own access environment as necessary. The service domain operates outside the bank but is included in the landscape as it may run application capabilities that are either provided by or certified for use by the bank.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain represents customer side devices. Most commonly providing a customer access portal to the banks products and services through any suitable channel and device.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain represents customer side devices. Most commonly providing a customer access portal to the banks products and services through any suitable channel and device.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A customer downloads an end-user financial management application offered by the bank."/>
