<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Contact Dialogue"
    id="7ce48e4e-19f9-423b-800e-748e951e1dd5"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A customer dials the contact center with an account balance request. The customer identity is checked by the rep (using a Party Profile service operation). After the customer question has been answered the dialogue is structured to attempt a sales pitch for an internal campaign that the customer has been preapproved for as flagged in their Party Profile record&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;The Customer dialogue handling capability provides a highly structured orchestration capability to leverage any customer interaction by consolidating customer related data and using the session (and any additional intelligence and context data gleaned during the dialogue) to leverage the interaction. In a more advance implementation the customer interaction capabilities could be integrated into an automated self/service context in addition to the more conventional CSR support utility. The structured customer dialogue leverages the opportunity by checking for other business activities that may be worked into the session for example, delivering pending communications, sales/marketing, capturing intelligence/triggers, updating status, product fulfillment (such as synchronizing customer-side data sets). The facility can be multi-channel/multi-device&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Handle/structure the customer narrative - consolidate and present data and guidelines, provide standard dialogue/scripting, provoke questions when appropriate capture key data including relationship and sales triggers. Ensure the correct sequencing, content and derived actions are performed/initiate. Leverage the session as appropriate to provide customer notifications, status updates and undertake sales/marketing efforts.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент набирает контакт-центр с запросом баланса счета. Идентификация клиента проверяется представителем (с помощью операции Службы профилей сторон). После ответа на вопрос клиента диалог структурируется таким образом, чтобы попытаться сделать шаг продаж для внутренней кампании, для которой клиент был предварительно утвержден как отмеченный в записи профиля участника&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Обработка диалога заказчик обеспечивает высокоструктурированную возможности оркестрации использовать любые взаимодействия с клиентами за счет консолидации данных, касающихся поддержки и помощи сессии (и любые дополнительные разведки и связи сведения, почерпнутые в ходе диалога), чтобы рычаги взаимодействия. В более продвинутой реализации возможности взаимодействия с клиентами могут быть интегрированы в автоматизированный контекст самообслуживания в дополнение к более традиционной утилите поддержки КСО. Структурированный диалог с клиентами использует эту возможность, проверяя другие бизнес-операции, которые могут быть обработаны в сеансе, например, доставку ожидающих сообщений, продажи / маркетинг, захват интеллекта/триггеров, обновление статуса, выполнение продукта (например, синхронизация наборов данных на стороне клиента). Средство может быть multi-channel / multi-прибором&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Обрабатывать / структурировать повествование клиента-консолидировать и представлять данные и рекомендации, обеспечивать стандартный диалог/сценарии, провоцировать вопросы, когда это необходимо захват ключевых данных, включая отношения и продажи триггеров. Гарантируйте правильную последовательность, содержание и производные действия выполнены / инициируют. Использовать сессии как надлежащие уведомления клиента, обновления статуса и осуществления продаж/маркетинга.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;__связан с 45 сервис доменами&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Contact Dialog&#xA;The customer contact dialogue handling capability can provide highly structured orchestration to streamline a customer interaction by consolidating and presenting customer related data in context. It can also use the session to gather additional customer intelligence. In a more advance implementation the customer interaction capabilities can be integrated into an automated self/service context in addition to the more conventional assisted service model. The structured customer dialogue can include tasks to check for other business activities that can be built into the exchange for example, delivering pending communications, sales/marketing attempts, capturing intelligence/triggers, updating relationship status/details, product fulfillment (such as synchronizing customer-side data). The facility can be designed to support multi-channel/multi-device deployments&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain handles/structures the customer narrative during an interactive session. It consolidates and presents pertinent customer information and provides servicing guidelines with standard dialogue/scripting as appropriate. It can include the capability to provoke questions to capture key relationship and sales triggers. It also ensures the correct sequencing, dialogue content and actions are performed/initiated during the customer interaction. It may further leverage the session by passing on customer notifications, status updates and triggering sales/marketing efforts&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;Structures the customer narrative during an interactive session. It consolidates and presents customer information and provides servicing guidelines with standard dialogue. It can include the capability to provoke questions to capture key relationship and sales triggers&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A customer dials into the contact center with a current account balance request. The customer identity is checked. After the customer initial query has been addressed the dialogue is structured to attempt a sales pitch for an internal campaign that the customer has been pre-approved for as flagged&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;"/>
