<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Underwriting"
    id="31c5fcdb-9a1d-414f-b17f-3afc415bc693"
    documentation="&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A corporate loan offer is processed and at the appropriate point an underwriting authorization is requested based on the presented details of the loan (terms, credit standing, collateral coverage etc.)&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;Underwriting is a specific authorization stage in writing a loan where different aspects of the loan are considered including the credit standing, collateral coverage, loan terms and other customer related factors such as history/prospects and segment positioning. For larger loans the underwriting decision can be influenced by strategic goals and capital allocations of the enterprise. Underwriting also applies to insurance products that are not currently in scope of the BIAN Service Landscape&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Manage the underwriting decision process and different levels of authorization required for proposed loans&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Предложение корпоративного кредитного обрабатывается и в соответствующий момент авторизации, андеррайтинга предлагается на основании представленных сведений по кредиту (условия, положение кредита, залогового покрытия и т. д.)&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Андеррайтинг-это особый этап авторизации при оформлении кредита, на котором рассматриваются различные аспекты кредита, включая кредитоспособность, покрытие залога, условия кредита и другие факторы, связанные с клиентами, такие как история/перспективы и позиционирование сегмента. Для крупных кредитов на решение андеррайтинга могут влиять стратегические цели и распределение капитала предприятия. Андеррайтинг также распространяется на страховые продукты, которые в настоящее время не входят в сферу услуг BIAN&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Управление процессом принятия решений по андеррайтингу и различными уровнями авторизации, необходимыми для предлагаемых кредитов&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Underwriting&#xA;The underwriting decision considers the ability of the borrower to finance the loan based on their known cash flows and credit worthiness. The underwriting decision refers to specific properties of the proposed loan (amount, term, repayment schedule, collateral etc.), the income and known commitments of the borrower and their credit history with the bank. The decision may factor perceived underwriting risks into the interest rate and/or collateral requirements to obtain approval.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain manages the underwriting decision process for loan origination.&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain manages the underwriting decision process for loan origination.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A corporate loan offer is processed and at the appropriate point an underwriting authorization is requested.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;- A management process governing the evaluation and assumption of risk&#xA;- Процесс управления, регулирующий оценку и принятие риска&#xA;"/>
