<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Card Clearing"
    id="90422946-1aa1-482b-a48f-2554b4c67997"
    documentation="&#xA;&#xA;Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;An Acquiring Bank receives charge transactions submitted by Merchants through Point of Sale Terminals or batch submission for recurring billing and forwards these transactions to the respective Card Issuing Banks through the Card Network (e.g. Visa, MC, AMEX, Diners, etc.). This process may take place multiple times during the day.&#xA;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;This service domain is used by a Card Acquiring Bank for consolidating all incoming transactions from Merchants, determining their routing, and transmitting to the respective Card Networks. It is used by the Card Networks to receive and consolidate the transactions from all Acquiring Banks and to distribute and route them to the respective Card Issuing Banks. It is also used by the Card Issuing Banks to receive their cardholder transactions from the Card Networks and to route them to the instance of the Credit/Charge Card service domain which is responsible for the card used in the transaction. The transactions may include charges, refunds, and chargebacks.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Orchestate: &#xA;&#x9;a) the capture and consolidation of card financial transactions originating from various sources, such as POS Network, E-Commerce Gateway, ATM Network, or Card Case Management, and &#xA;&#x9;b) clearing of the transactions from the Acquirers to the Issuers through the Card Networks&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Банк-эквайер получает платежные транзакции, отправленные продавцами через терминалы продажи или пакетную отправку для периодического выставления счетов, и направляет эти транзакции соответствующим банкам-эмитентам карт через сеть карт (например, Visa, MC, AMEX, Diners и т. д.).). Этот процесс может происходить несколько раз в течение дня.&#xA;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Этот сервисный домен используется банком-эквайером карт для консолидации всех входящих транзакций от продавцов, определения их маршрутизации и передачи в соответствующие карточные сети. Он используется сетями карт для приема и консолидации транзакций от всех банков-эквайеров, а также для распределения и маршрутизации их в соответствующие банки-эмитенты карт. Он также используется банками-эмитентами карт для получения их операций с держателями карт из сетей карт и направить их к экземпляру домена обслуживания кредитных / платежных карт, который отвечает за карту, используемую в транзакции. Транзакции могут включать сборы, возврат и возвратные платежи.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Orchestate: &#xA;&#x9;а) захват и консолидация карточных финансовых операций, происходящих из различных источников, таких как сеть POS, шлюз электронной коммерции, сеть банкоматов или управление карточным делом, и &#xA;&#x9;Б) очистка транзакций от эквайеров эмитентам через карточные сети&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Card Clearing&#xA;The behavior varies depending on the role of the participant bank/network. A card acquiring Bank consolidates all incoming transactions from Merchants, determining their routing, and transmitting to the respective Card Networks. For the Card Networks it receives and consolidates the transactions from all Acquiring Banks and to distribute and route them to the respective Card Issuing Banks. For the Card Issuing Banks it receives their cardholder transactions from the Card Networks and routes them to the instance of the Credit/Charge Card service domain which is responsible for the card used in the transaction. The transactions may include charges, refunds, and chargebacks.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This orchestrates the capture and consolidation of card financial transactions originating from various sources, such as POS Network, E-Commerce Gateway, ATM Network, or Card Case Management. It also handles the clearing of the transactions from the Acquirers to the Issuers through the Card Network&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;An Acquiring Bank receives charge transactions submitted by Merchants through Point of Sale Terminals or batch submission for recurring billing and forwards these transactions to the respective Card Issuing Banks through the Card Network. This process may take place multiple times during the day.&#xA;"/>
