<archimate:BusinessService
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Current Account"
    id="42a0e7f5-c976-45f3-bd42-9a52a3839a05"
    documentation=" Example of use:&#xA;&#xA;A customer processes a series of services (e.g., request printed statements, initiate a transfer, set up a standing order) through the call center using their current account&#xA;&#xA;General comment:&#xA;&#xA;The Current Account or Demand Deposit Account as it can be called is a financial facility that represents the general checking account facility at the core of the consumer and small business banking activity. There is a range of supporting features that make up the standard facility (checks/cheques, standing orders, debit cards, phone and on-line banking services etc.). The fulfillment will include a range of optional services, fees and interest payments and penalties and will often be bundled and or underlie/support other financial facilities and financial transactions&#xA;&#xA;Business Purpose&#xA;:  Orchestrate a consumer checking/demand deposit account with typical range of services and fees&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Пример использования:&#xA;&#xA;Клиент обрабатывает ряд услуг (например, запрашивает распечатанные выписки, инициирует перевод, оформляет постоянный заказ) через колл-центр, используя свой текущий счет&#xA;&#xA;Общее замечание:&#xA;&#xA;Текущий счет или депозитный счет до востребования, как его можно назвать, представляет собой финансовый механизм, который представляет собой общий расчетный счет в основе банковской деятельности потребителей и малого бизнеса. Существует целый ряд вспомогательных функций, которые составляют стандартный объект (чеки, постоянные поручения, дебетовые карты, телефонные и он-лайн банковских услуг и т. д.). Выполнение будет включать в себя ряд дополнительных услуг, сборов и процентных платежей и штрафов и часто будет в комплекте и или лежать в основе/поддержки других финансовых средств и финансовых операций&#xA;&#xA;деловая цель&#xA;: Организовать  потребителя проверочный/ депозитный счет до востребования с типичным спектром услуг и сборов&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Service Domain - Current Account&#xA;The Current Account or Demand Deposit Account as it can be called is a financial facility that represents the general checking account facility at the core of the consumer and small business banking activity. There is a range of supporting features that make up the standard facility (checks/cheques, standing orders, debit cards, phone and on-line banking services etc.). The fulfillment can include a range of optional services, fees and interest payments and penalties and will often be bundled and or underlie/support other financial facilities and financial transactions.&#xA;&#xA;Detailed Summary&#xA;This service domain orchestrates a consumer checking/demand deposit account. The typical range of services and fees covers payments and deposits, standing orders, sweeps, liens, check and debit card access.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Executive Summary&#xA;This service domain orchestrates a consumer checking/demand deposit account. The typical range of services and fees covers payments and deposits, standing orders, sweeps, liens, check and debit card access.&#xA;&#xA;Examples Of Use&#xA;A customer processes a series of services (e.g., request printed statements, initiate a transfer, set up a standing order) through the call center by accessing their current account.&#xA;"/>
